Claude has changed social media forever.
You can now create content in minutes,
build your brand, your business, saving
you time [music] and money. But most
advice out there says a lot and shows
you nothing. I've been doing social
media marketing for over 10 years, and
in the last 2 years I've gone allin on
AI, improving my workflows, [music]
systems to make me a better creator. So
today, I'm bringing you a full course
exactly how to use claw to get more
followers, make more money, and stop
guessing. My name is Alex. Let's jump
into it. AI has changed everything for
those of us trying to do something on
social media. It can now design. It can
now edit. It can now write. It can now
research. It can now schedule. What used
to potentially take a week or hundreds
of dollars can be done in an afternoon.
And it took something as well. A lot of
us have actually stopped thinking. The
tool got good enough that we don't make
decisions anymore. We just sit back. But
the issue with that is that everyone is
doing that. It all looks the same. same
tools, same prompts, same output. Hey,
look at my hook. Everyone arrived at the
same place and it's frustrating. So, you
might be in this situation right now.
Even though you're using AI, it's
telling you everything, you're not
getting the results. 40 minutes of
fighting it to get something worse than
what you would have originally made.
I've been there many times and you'll
see the way I built this course. This is
about you being the captain of this
ship. If you've come here to think that
you're going to be sitting on a beach,
you know, sipping coconut water, you're
just going to press one button and
you're going to be a millionaire, this
is not for you. But I will show you how
I've been able to save tons of time
every month, hours and hours, replace
multiple people on my team, and make
more output, get better results.
But it's taken me some time to get to
this point, which is now why I've put
this together, and you're here. But
please pay attention to this. Now, as I
said, I did all of it, you know, posted
things I had not read properly,
published stuff I would have never
written, made more and it worked less.
Guys, please keep the speed, get the
thinking back. The goal is for us to be
this leader of our business, of our
idea. You are watching this and you have
a unique idea that I have no idea about,
that your neighbor has no idea about,
that no one does. Okay? So, it's about
us. AI is going to give us that ability
to make this a reality. So, what I've
built is going to put that power in your
hands. Okay? AI does the work. You make
the call. It still sounds like you. I I
want you to be you. I don't want you to
be Claude. Let's get this party started.
Okay. Who is this course for? This is
for you if you make content yourself.
Okay. and you're tired of potentially
spending a lot of time on it, wasting a
lot of money, and looking like everyone
else. You run a business on your own,
and you do not have a team behind you.
Okay? I've had multiple people on my
team. I've spent hundreds of thousands
on on freelancers, designers, team
members, and I've been able to replace a
big portion of that team because of AI.
And you can do the exact same thing if
you start to understand what we're
building in this video. Social media can
become much easier for you. If you do
this for others and have clients, then
this is also for you. I've been a social
media manager many years when I was
younger and I know how much time it
takes and this will definitely free up a
ton of time with you for you whilst
maintaining that high level that we're
always going for. So the stuff that
we're going to actually build today in
this course, eight brains that you know
that know your brand, audience and
business and those brains are
gamechanging. Okay. Um 20 skills doing
the work you keep repeating. So you will
learn about skills which are massive. 30
days of content from one idea. A way to
tell whether any of it is actually good.
a visual system Claude follows every
single time. Carousels, images, and
video on demand. So, you'll actually be
able to create content with this,
showing you how Claude can do that for
you. And then finally, an offer, a
funnel, and a full email sequence. So, I
deserve a like already, don't I? And a
subscribe if you haven't. Um, but you
are going to get a ton of value in this.
And these are just, you know, me
summarizing these hours into six points
or seven points. There's going to be
more. You're going to learn a lot. Get a
notepad. You know, take your time with
it. Save the video, download it, do what
you need to do. Okay, this is a game
changer. So, there's we've split this up
into three different sections. So, we
have the think section, think section,
which is 15 minutes, no tools, the
decisions you have to make before
anything else. Okay? So, and every
section is important, okay? Okay?
Because you can't just build without
thinking. Build the bulk of it. Screen
recording through the whole way. So you
will see that there is multiple
different kind of build moments.
Essentially all of that is where you're
going to learn hands-on how I create
these workflows that build this system.
And then finally, we'll have the judge
stage, which is what AI cannot do for
you and what you can actually start
doing once you've completed this course,
a plan for you. So every step is going
to be extremely impactful. Let's jump
into it.
Okay. So, it would be a Claude video
without a real understanding of all the
different models. So, when we go on to
Claude, there will be different models
that we can pick from. Okay. So, for
example, right now there are four
different ones. So, you got Hiku, you
got Sonet, you got Opus, and Fable.
These two are the ones that normally
people use. Although there's a lot of
hype at the moment about fable over time
some of these might go. So you might be
watching this video and HQ might not
exist but what I'm teaching you here is
not about specifically like the names of
the models but the understanding of how
they work. Okay. So for example normally
with all um kind of AI models you'll
have different ones. Okay. And how they
work is like this. So it's like a
business. You have an apprentice which
is Hu. You have your daily driver which
means your kind of uh low cost uh that
can do kind of the basic tasks which is
set in this case. You have your manager
which is higher costs remember we have
to pay for AI usage even on a paid plan
you know you get credits etc which get
um renewed then you have opus which is
like your manager and then you have
fable which is your architect. So you
can see for example it goes from low to
high in terms of cost. You know Fable
costs way more to run than HU. So when
we're using AI we want to understand
this. Okay. So when we're you know it's
not about using opus kind of for
everything because there's certain tasks
which are just going to save us a lot of
um credits simply by using sonet and
we'll get the same output. And it's the
same thing with fable. Fable is a really
really good um you know pioneering AI
model but it builds the system. It
doesn't do my basic tasks. So, if I'm
creating skills, if I'm creating um you
know, specific big prompts, big
workflows, you know, there might be
parts in this video where I'm using
Opus, where I'm using Sonet, and you
might think, you know what, I'm actually
going to use Fable for that and have a
prompt that I can, you know, a strong
prompt that I use, you know, all the
time going forward. And I want you to
just understand that. So, Fable is like
for specific things, you know, kind of
one-time things that you will do. Okay,
I need a really good project file for
that. I need a really good prompt for
that. I'll use fable. Then switch over
to for example sonet or opus. Okay,
there are certain things that we can uh
use it for. Although I do recommend kind
of sitting around here and then moving
to fable. So for example, you'll see you
know exactly what I mean. So fable in a
logic builds the brain. Okay, so this is
kind of a one long session builds a
brain which then allows it to turns it
into skills and projects. Then Sonet for
example can run that every day or you
can run it on Opus. So you've got the
kind of two choices and hand uh HQ is
able to handle kind of the boring tasks.
Now this depends on the workflows etc
and you'll see throughout the video but
you need to be able to kind of
differentiate this. Okay, do not spend
all your time on Fable. You can spend
all your time here, but you still want
to use Fable. Okay, so essentially
building a brand from scratch, building
a brain, brand brain from scratch. So if
you see me doing a brand brain in this
video and I'm using Opus, use Fable. And
if there's a new model when you you're
watching this which is higher than Fable
or replaces Sonic, etc., you just need
to mix and match. It's this simple and
you'll always be able to understand
which is which. Turning one article into
a month of content. Opus everyday
posting, captions, edits. If you have a
very strict formula for your captions
which fable has produced for you, boom,
you can use sonic for that. Okay,
default is usually right. Okay, so when
we go to claude, you'll see that there
is the models, then there's the effort.
Okay, with this it means you know how
much effort is that kind of prompt or
that specific thought uh generation
going to take. Okay, some of them will
have extra you know extra low whatever.
I recommend going usually with the
default unless it's like a researchbased
one or you really, you know, you're at
the limit with Fable, you know, you're,
you know, you can and you can want to
push things, then obviously you can go
higher, but usually the default works
very much enough. Uh, very much uh,
yeah, enough. The names change, but the
frameworks don't. You will see me switch
models throughout this video or this
course, and the versions have moved on
by the time you watch it. It just
happens, you know. I'll go to bed today
and wake up and it's chat GBT 29. It's
Claude 58. It's Nano Banana 70. If you
understand this framework, you can
decide which model to use for anything I
show you. Want to hand manage a job to
the architect? Do it. Your call, your
credits. It's the logic that we're
playing with. It's it's it's the thought
process, the workflow. Okay? You just
from watching this part understand
exactly how the models work. Okay? So to
make this video possible, Hicksfield
have sponsored it. Now Hicksfield are
one of my sponsors, but they are also
one of the tools that I use every single
day. So essentially in Hicksfield, this
is what's going to allow us to create
our content. Okay. So when I'm using
Claude and I want to use, you know,
image generation models, video
generation models, um I'm able to do
that because I've connected it with my
MCP
in Claude. Okay. So if I press MCP,
you'll see all I need to do is follow
these steps. You'd copy this, go to
connectors on Claude, and boom, you'd
have Higfield inside Claude, which is
going to allow us to do everything in
this kind of course in terms of image
generation, video generation, etc.
Hicksfield is my favorite platform for
this because it makes the whole process
soon as soon as there's a new kind of
model chatgbt image 2 etc. Then
essentially it will be available and
that means it's available in your
claude. Okay. So for example nano banana
pro chatgbt image 2. You might be
watching this and it's chatgbt 57 you
know it will be available and that just
means my workflow you know when I first
started using AI you know you'd have to
go to this platform then that platform
then this platform then that whereas now
I'm just in claude with a connection to
Higsville via the MCP and this makes my
life so much easier now you can see you
know I use it to do my color grading you
know this is one of my thumbnails
playing around with the color grading um
amazing stuff you know it's and I'm able
to do all of this uh with the power of
Hixfold. Now, there are a few other good
things as well to, you know, look at as
well. There's like image upscale, phase
swap, um you know, for video, it's the
exact same thing. You know, video
upscale. So, if you have a video that's
kind of low quality, 720p, whatever, 10,
and you want to upscale it to 4K, for
example, it's all available here. And it
works in a similar way to like the
credit system. Um I mean, most AIs are
credit system, but the price point works
well. The most beautiful part of it all
is that it just connects with Claude and
the process is smooth. So, you will see
throughout this video how we're able to
create an insane amount of content fast
just due to this connection. The link
will be in the description for you to
explore Higsfield so that you can create
content with the power of Claude. Okay.
So, you have the models and you
understand Claude, but it doesn't have
any way for it to know who you are. So
most of the outputs are just going to be
generic. Well, now we're going to build
the single document that it will be able
to read from. Essentially, it's brain
and soul which come from you. Let's jump
into it. Hey everyone, just a quick
disclaimer that this YouTube course does
have some of my existing YouTube videos,
but it's been cut up and I've added a
ton of new content to it as well so that
it reads and feels more like a course so
that you could just stick to one video
and kind of go through the whole process
so that you can understand how Claude
can impact your social media the best
way. So this is kind of a you know
compilation of everything plus more on
top so that you can get a clean flow of
everything from start to finish so that
you can maximize your clawed and social
media gains.
Okay. So it begins now before we jump
into the good stuff you know the visuals
the brand building we need to set the
foundations. Now as I've said there are
multiple different brains. Okay. So to
have a full system you need all the
brains together. But for example, today
we're building the visual brain. So what
I want to do first is just build a
foundation so that even if you have only
a visual brain, this still works super
well. So what we're going to do is build
a foundation. Now for this, essentially
the goal is for us to create the visual
brain. Okay? But this doesn't just come
out of Finette. You know, we need to
understand why we're building. What's it
for? So we're going to go through very
quickly. Trust me, this takes about 5 10
seconds. But you need to follow the
steps from this point on in the video.
If you just download the documents I
provide and answer them, you are going
to miss the way I'm telling you to
answer them because it makes a massive
difference and 10 minutes extra of your
time is going to make all the
difference. So for the visuals with
intelligence, not just aesthetics. Okay,
we're feeding the visual brain with
intelligence, not just aesthetics.
Identity, audience, voice, we will get
the visual brain. Once we get to the
visual brain, we're going to start
building. So identity, what does this
mean? So one sentence, let's say, I'm a
content strategist. No, it's better to
say I help overwhelmed business owners
create content that brings them clients.
It's going to help Claude more. Three,
five brand words. You know, this is more
about how your brand should feel, the
atmosphere when someone experiences it,
you know, so bold, minimal, premium,
raw, clean, calm, intense, you know, so
these are all singular lines. What
you're not is super important because
going forward, you want to make sure
that Claude doesn't venture into these
categories. So, these kind of negative
prompts, bold, but not aggressive, you
know, minimal but not cold. I'm going to
show you how to do this quickly. So,
don't worry. So, understand your
audience. For example, I've been doing
this so long. I understand my audience,
although I'm always researching. But if
you don't understand your audience that
well, you can go to your DMs or comments
or your competitors. You can go on to
Reddit, YouTube comments, X. There's so
many places that you can find stuff. So,
for example, let's say I was doing
something in productivity or for this
project, you know, I am. So, I'm going
to press or type in productivity up
here. And then what I would do is type
in like struggles. And that will show me
everyone that's typed in a title with
like struggle. And then what I can do
is, you know, press like top or
something all time. You're not lazy, you
know, etc., etc. [music]
So, for example, this one, okay, the box
breathing technique, you know, and you
want to see what people are talking
about, you know, what they're struggling
with, etc. And you'll get a lot of
information from this and you can just
screenshot it and put it into Claude.
Now, let's jump into Claude. So, the
first thing we want to do, so we're not
creating a project yet. What I want you
to do is grab one of the documents I've
provided, which is the foundation
document. So, let me grab that. [music]
So, this is a simple foundation builder.
Okay? So, you want to just slap that in
there and press start. And this is going
to be super important when we get to the
visual builder. So, you just simply want
to answer the questions. Okay? So, it
shouldn't take you long. You'll get a
very simple document which you can then
take to the next part. Okay? So, three
sections, identity, audience, voice, ask
you a few questions as I've just shown
you right here. You know, it's all here
and it's all going to really help you.
Okay, so remember your audience visual
taste matters. Again, this is a bit of
research. Light backgrounds, dark
backgrounds, but we're going to go into
more visuals later on. Voice, why it
matters. Now, the voice is super
important before I move on to the
branding and the visuals. What this
means is Claude is going to be creating
content for you. Visuals, yes, branding,
but the way you present your ideas is
super important. So just to give two
kind of similarities or differences,
establishing a consistent morning
routine can significantly enhance your
productivity and overall well-being
throughout the day. So this is without
my voice rules, but with my voice rules,
your morning routine isn't working.
Here's why. So for me, I want my brand
or my, you know, what I'm building to be
direct to the point and sharp. And for
me, that's going to be super important.
So that's when there's, you know, any
times where kind of Claude is waffling
or not giving me what I want, it knows,
you know what, we're just going to go
boom, straight to the point. And this is
really, really important. You'll be able
to find your rules. You know, it's not
too difficult. Okay, the gap between
these two lists, your voice rules. Stop
planning. Start with one thing. Unlock
your full potential with these
strategies. You know, this doesn't sound
like me. And Claude is going to guide
you on this. If you're struggling with
any of these, just ask it and you can
take it from there. Okay. So, you have
what you say and who you say it to, but
you don't have how any of this is going
to look on social media. So, now it's
time to work on the colors, fonts, and
layout rules because this is where the
magic starts to happen.
Strap in because this is where it's
going to get fun. So, this is your
visual brain that we're about to build.
Please pay attention because what I'm
about to show you is super super useful
and it's going to help you so much. Drop
a like. Okay, so this is roughly, you
know, what it will look like. Obviously,
this is a lot bigger than the foundation
one. So, let's just run it and jump into
it. Now, what we're going to do is
basically head over to Claude and what
you want to do is again build a new
chat. Okay, so we're just going to do
this again in new chat and then we'll
start moving to projects later. But we
have the brain box foundation which we
just created with the foundation. Then
you want to grab my visual brain builder
again which will be available for you
and you want to put these into the chat
and press start. Now I've already
started just so that we can skip a few
steps so you can see and essentially it
will start asking you questions and
helping you build your brand system,
your visual system, brain um and you can
see right here. So, do you already have
brand [music] colors? No. Suggest a
palette for me. Boom. And it will start
suggesting palettes. Now, I'm going to
show you a few ways to also get your own
ideas and not just rely on Claude. So,
for example, color palette. How does
this color palette feel? This palette is
perfect. Okay, great. What background,
you know, what carousels, etc. Remember,
this is specifically for carousels. Now,
what you want to do for color, I
wouldn't suggest just listening to
Claude based on the foundation. You want
to go with your own vision as well. What
we're going to do is head over to this
website right here. So, coolers, colors,
I don't know. Um, but essentially you'll
be able to do a lot of color theory
work, understanding the color palettes
that you want. This is so so important
to explore 10 million different
palettes. And you can see that there's
different tools like the color contrast
checker, which is super important for
carousels. You don't want colors that
blend in together. But basically, it
will show you colors that match
together. So, for example, if I type in
black or pick black, it will show me,
okay, this is a palette that works. And
what you want to do then is press
visualize colors. And you can then get
all of these kind of [music] examples of
how these colors work together. This is
so important for creating content
because a lot of people get colors
wrong. Now, they've got so many
different options here. Color picker,
everything you need. You can type in a
specific color and you can start from
there. So, cherry rose and it will give
you the hex code, which you can see I've
got right here. And you can start
building from that. And you can even
give Claude one specific hex code and
say, okay, I want to start with this
one. You know what colors would match
this? [music] If you want a high
contrast color palette, it will suggest
colors that have high contrast against
it. If you want colors that are warm
together, so orange, red, white, you
want that to be your palette, it will do
that and it'll be able to start building
that for you. So, it's super important
to spend some time on this because color
is going to be a key component for you.
So, for me, I've gone with this color
way right here. Now, you can see right
here, it's giving me the suggestions,
you know, how does this color palette
feel? I'm just typing any question. But
the way it asks questions is super
useful. So, yes, I have fonts. No, I
don't. So, I'm going to put yes, I have
fonts. And for fonts, what you want to
do, two different options. So you want
to use this website right here, font
joy. And essentially, this shows you
visual hierarchy of fonts. So typography
hierarchy. The really good carousels on
Instagram have different typography.
Okay? So it's not just one font. So
you'd have a headline font, potentially
a subheading font, body font, a CTA
font. And this just gives you more
visual contrast, and it allows the eye
to move like a ping-pong ball. So it
keeps people engaged, and it's just
basic kind of hierarchy for typography.
This website right here will, you know,
you just press generate. It will show
you different combinations. You can add
combinations. Now, if you want to just
find general fonts that suit you, Claude
can give you input for all of these, but
I do recommend you spending some time
and looking at at doing your own
research cuz you will find your own
creativity. And we'll get to that in a
point. But you can see here 101 fonts,
tons of different fonts. You know, you
can just type in handwriting, bold,
whatever you are feeling. Again, Google
fonts. You know, if I want a medieval
font, boom, here are the medieval fonts.
You know, if I'm doing something
medieval, they're right here. And then I
have them. And I can insert that
information to Claude. For example, I
would just grab this and say [music]
Times New Roman. You know, everyone
knows that font. And you can build it
that way.
Okay. So, we're about to jump into some
mood boarding. Now, this is super
important because one of the hardest
things about creating content is
inspiration. Okay? And inspiration or
creativity can actually comes from
external factors. So, your environment.
And a mood board is going to help you
have constant reference points, whether
it's visually, whether it's, you know,
branding to give to Claude. So, we're
about to jump into that right now. And
your creative stack would look something
like this. So, let's jump into that
right now. So, that you have a creative
system as well. Pinterest is going to be
your best friend. I've created a new
account for this project. I'm going to
go to your boards and you're going to
create new board. Then, in your new
board, it will look something like this.
And what you want to do is start
building your visual identity, your
creative stack. This is super important
for your brand. Anytime I need
inspiration, whether it's for colors,
creativity, images, for none of an
honor, it's all going to be here based
on my brand. And in 10 minutes, you can
save 88 pins and boom, you're ready, you
know. So, anytime I need some ideas or
anything, it's all here. And you can
even base your brand off this. This
creativity mood board is super
important. And this is going to help you
as well with the next part, which is
kind of your layout and composition.
With your carousels, you need to decide,
you know, what type of text do you want?
Do you want kind of these longer texts?
Do you want big bold text? You know, you
need to really do your research and
think about that. But this is going to
be important because otherwise Claude is
or AI is just going to throw random
stuff at you. No rules visual brand
applied. Again, text positioning on
images. Again, I want it to not overlay
my images. So, for example, if I have
this image right here, I don't want
Claude to suddenly put text on top of
this. Okay? So, it needs to understand
to put it, you know, in the corner. So,
that again is super important. The next
thing content architecture the way the
content flows and Claude is going to
guide you through this. Okay, so visual
rhythm means you know especially for
carousels means how they kind of change.
So slide two will be much brighter and
this just helps with retention. So you
would just keep answering these
questions and at the end you will
basically have your visual brain which
is going to really be so important for
you going forward. And if you want me to
make more videos and you like this
topic, how to use AI as a content
creator, as a social media marketer for
different elements, please let me know.
But the brain is a big thing for me. You
know, the psychology brain is a huge
factor. The audience brain strategy,
these specific ones are just examples.
My brains, I have a ton of them which I
use independently and together in
multiple different scenarios. So you can
see here as I showed you at the
beginning, the final kind of one for me.
So we we talked through the audience. We
got the voice rules. We've got the color
system. We've got the typography, image
direction, you know, the aesthetic,
storytelling, few visuals, you know,
I've got the slide positioning, I've got
the layout, compositioning, I got text
positioning, I got the margins and safe
zones, I got text on image, contrast
rules, density, all of this. Think about
how much information this is now for
Claude when it creates your carousels in
this world where millions and millions
of people are creating the same content.
Okay, so here's a quick summary of the
visual brain. This is super important,
you know, because with your visual
brain, you can add more to it over time.
So, if there's a carousel or you make
[music] a change with your logo,
anything you want to add, you can add it
over time. Remember that system that
Claude can reference it at any time. But
this is kind of the basic. I want you to
screenshot and tick and get ready for
your kind of system to begin that visual
brain checklist. So, you can simply
screenshot this, take stuff, understand
it, and we can move on. But this will
help you so much. But remember, over
time, you can add to it, you can tweak
it. You know, my prompts you can tweak.
They are not the final prompts. They are
to help you understand, to get you
going. You know, if there's a particular
one, you know, you want to make eight
slides, you want to do four slides,
[music] that's on you to identify that.
But this is going to get you started in
a completely different way.
Okay. So now we've got our visual brain
document. We're going to create a new
project. And this means that now any
chat in this project, it's going to have
this visual brain backing it. So I'm
going to call visual brain like the
video. Create project. And boom. What
you would add here is your document. So
the document that you would have just
created which is right here. I'm going
to literally put all of this like this.
Press copy and boom. Have it in my
instructions. Paste the instructions
right here. Save instructions. And now
you have your visual brain. So now we're
going to actually create some content
using this. Okay. So what we're going to
do is we're going to paste this prompt
which is similar to the previous video.
Very similar. Again prompting can be
better but for the purpose of this video
I'm going to grab an article. So, I've
got an article right here. So, last
video I did my YouTube script, but for
this project, I want to do something
different. I'm going to put this article
right here, and let's see what it comes
up with. So, I'm going to press this
right here. So, I'll see you in a sec.
Now, of course, something I haven't
mentioned as well is the logo building.
I'm not going to go into today, but
creating your logo once you have a color
palette, etc. You can even ask Claude,
use Nano Banana, use, you know, I'm sure
I've actually mentioned it in videos how
to create logos. Maybe I'll put
something up here. Um, but you can use
virtually anything to create a logo. But
once you have your colors, once you have
your typography and things like that,
everything like logos, etc. becomes a
lot easier. Now part of your brand um or
your brain, you could add your logo as a
reference point, you know, to always add
the CTA slide, etc., etc. So, you can
take this to another level. So, you can
quickly see following the rules value
reset near black.
You can always just press this [music]
and see how Claud is kind of working
through its process. We've got our
results. So, this is the first one. So,
based on that prompt you just saw,
here's what we have. So, if I open this
up here, sometimes what I like to do is
do the HTML first before I do PNG, just
so that I can get it. So, for an initial
one, it's not too bad. Now, I did change
my branding slightly because I want it
to be a bit more warm and have this
certain color way, but in terms of what
it's done initially, it's not bad. Okay,
now obviously we can do way better than
[music] this, but for an initial, you
know, first time with the visuals, it's
followed kind of the visuals that we
want, you know, followed the branding.
But now we're going to take this to
another level because there's no images
and we can do better than this. But for
a start, it's not too bad. The main
[music] thing that I've wanted here is
that is followed kind of the patterns
that I've interpreted in the visual
brain.
So before we build anything, you need to
know exactly what you're building
because branding isn't one thing, it's
four. And almost every creator, social
media I look at, even the ones doing
well, has maybe one of them. [music] Two
if they're lucky. why their page looks
fine but doesn't feel like anything. A
real brand has four and [music] they all
agree with each other. So pillar one is
positioning and this is who your content
is for. And trust me, I'm going to show
you everything what you stand for, what
you're against. Most creators say
something like I help creators grow and
that tells me nothing. A real
positioning is sharp. I build content
system that drive leads, clients, and
revenue without the burner. Specific,
pointed. you know exactly [music] who
it's for and what it's against. Pillar
two is voice. This is how you sound. The
words you use, the words you'd [music]
never use. Here's the fast test. If
someone read your captions with your
name removed, would they know it's you?
For most creators, the answer is no.
[music] That's the gap. Your voice
should be consistent. It's recognizable
without your face on it. Now, the next
one is visual identity. And this is
where branding often ends up. This is
your palette, your fonts, your motives.
But the point isn't you have colors. The
point is that the colors mean something.
They're used the same way every time.
Most creators have a palette. [music]
Real brands have a system, a reason
every color is there, and a rule for
when each one shows up. If you want me
to make a bigger video about visual
identity, let me know in the comments.
Now, pillar four is [music] story. This
is the through line. Why you do this,
who you were before, what you believe
now. The thing that makes a stranger
care about your content before they
consumed any of it and most creators
completely skip this and then they
wonder why their content feels flat even
when their information is good. Now,
here's the part that most people miss.
The reason we split branding into
[music] four pillars isn't just to
organize it. It's to keep it dynamic.
Brands change, visuals get refined.
Stories evolve. If your brand,
especially with AI, is one big
undifferentiated thing. Every change
[music] means starting over with four
pillars. If your visuals need to shift,
you just update the visual document. The
other three stay locked in. That's how a
brand evolves without losing itself.
Now, when all four pillars agree with
each other, you stop having to make
brand decisions. The decisions are
already made. Every video, every
thumbnail, they all pull from the same
place. And that's when content stops
feeling like effort and starts feeling
like a system. And this is extremely
[music] important if you want to succeed
in the content world. So that's what
we're going to build. Positioning,
voice, visual identity, story, all four
in one document inside [music] Claude. I
call it the master brand brain. And once
you have it, you'll never look at your
content the same way again. So before I
build it, I want to show you what
looking at a brand through these four
pillars actually looks like. So I'm
going to do something that most brand
videos will never attempt to do, and
that's look at my own.
Okay. So for you to do this properly, we
need to first gather a few things. Okay,
I've made this so easy for you that you
better drop a like. The first thing is
gathering. So there are five different
things that basically we need to gather.
These go into audience, voice, visual,
offer and existing brand. Now if you are
a beginner or you have virtually
nothing, don't worry. I about to guide
you through this. So the first thing is
audience. To feed our brand, to build
our brand, to have this master brand
brain, it's only as smart as what you
feed it. We need to give it something at
the beginning. And going on Canva and
saying, "Oh, this is a nice color. Now
that's my brand." No, let me show you.
I've got all of these documents in my
vault and you can access everything
there. The vault is in the description.
You sign up, you get access to all my
resources from my videos. So the first
thing is this document right here. So
this is a layer of our brain. This
document holds everything you know about
the people you make content for. Okay.
The reason I've done it like this is
because you can get Claude to help you
go create this and do it. So, you could
just literally put it in there as well.
But I've done everything here for you.
So, where to find it? Instagram DMs and
YouTube comments, newsletter replies,
Reddit threads in your space,
competitive comment sections, customer
interviews and discovery calls, survey
responses and reviews. You can get
information about this stuff from right
here. So, this is a random old video
from one of my pages which is no longer
active. You know, if I wanted to, I've
got a post right here. I could just go
through the comments, screenshot some of
the comments that I care about or that I
think are impactful, top comments,
whatever. And then literally what you
would do is start putting it all in
here. And the reason I've done this is
because having documents like this makes
this dynamic. This brain is dynamic.
Then I could start feeding it with
information. This could be competitive
comments, this could be my comments,
this could be literally anything from
here. Reddit threads, newsletter
replies, anything. But you know right
here with this layer of audience we are
focusing on these particular things.
Okay honestly that easy. YouTube
comments anything like and you just
start pasting it in here. And obviously
here you know I've got my own example
who I'm looking for content creators
coaches consultants mostly 25 to 45 etc.
This is just an example. What hurts
posting consistently? So you should be
able to then start be able to answer
these questions. If you want to succeed
online you need to be able to answer
some of these eventually not right now
or if you can even better. Now the next
thing is voice. So voice brand isn't
just visuals, it's also your voice. How
do you sound? How do your scripts sound?
How do your captions sound? How do your
emails sound? How does anything that
requires kind of words make you sound?
What goes in here? So recent captions
again, newsletter intro. So you can
crossuse different things in in these if
they apply. So it will tell you uh where
to find it. Last 10 Instagram captions,
newsletter sense. So literally anything
that kind of has words, it will be
useful here. So, this is super important
because it start to tell you words I
use, words I don't use, the way you
interact. Because when you're creating
stuff in the future, whether it's a
script, whether it's an idea for a
newsletter, whether it's a product, you
don't want to have a certain style on
Instagram, and then you go on to your
product and it's clearly written by AI.
Hello, this is a 7-day plan to lose
weight, but online you're making jokes
and stuff. So, this is super important.
The next one is visual. So visual is the
standard one that everyone is mostly
when it comes to branding thinking
about. Okay. So this is mood boards,
Pinterest, love. This is where everyone
goes. So you can in here put brands and
creators who you visually admire,
specific references, colors you've drawn
to, you know, fonts, etc. You can just
throw that all in here and the document
or the brain will be able to reference
this at any point. And this is super
simple. I've shown this in videos
before. You know, you can go on to
websites like colorco etc. Fonts a
thousand1 to get fonts. It's all there
and you just throw them in here.
Honestly, just put them like there. You
can go on Pinterest, type in Moody
brand. You can see right here typed in
moody brand. I could type in green
brand. If I want to go with a specific
green and then you can start getting
kind of ideas from there, you know,
different contrast, different things.
And as you see us progress, you will see
how well this works. The next one is
offer. This one, some of you might not
be offering something, might not be
selling anything. That's fine. But
normally you should be or you should be
thinking about that. If you don't have
anything right now, put some stuff that
your competitors sell or that you think
you could sell in the future. This is
super important again because we're not
doing any of this for fun. I mean, I do
like it, but none of this is for fun.
This is business. This is social media.
This is content creation. This is our
job. So, we're doing this for a specific
purpose. So, you want to put information
like this in here. Okay? And remember,
this is going to allow us to answer
these questions. Okay, [music] these
questions are going to come from this
right here. So again, you know, offer.
Boom. The last one is existing brand. So
if you have existing things which you
like, which you want to improve, etc.
Just to give context, again, you can put
that into here. Okay. Now, of course,
the one I'm going to provide in the
vault is not going to have the examples.
You would literally, as I've just done
with the screenshots, just put stuff
into here. You can even put document
links from Google Drive, whatever you
want into here. But these documents will
be super important for you to work on.
These are dynamic documents. They don't
need to be perfect from day one. And I'm
going to explain later why it's
important to have these in separate
rather than just one massive document.
Okay. So now you know the next step.
We're going to go on to Claude. Go to
projects. New project. Boom. And what
you want to do is put in master brand
brain. So you can see I've just created
mine, but there is nothing in it. So,
I'm going to press master brain. Now,
here you have your project. Now, a
project is super important because this
keeps things condensed. And this is
where you have a specific use case for
your brand here. So, let's drop in our
file. So, the files we've just kind of
filled [music] in. Um, I'm going to just
grab them and just literally put them
into here. So, this is going to be our
reference point. So, you can see right
here, which is perfect. Now, we're going
to take this further. So, the point of
these is to build our pillars, which are
going to be the pillars that hold this
together. Now, this is the prompt that
I'm going to add for now. I'm going to
paste this in here. Nothing too
complicated. I'm going to go back, press
it again, and then I'm going to start a
conversation. Now, what you want to do
is start a new chat. And I'm going to
paste this in. So, we're building pillar
one, which is going to be the
positioning. And I'm going to press
enter. And then you will see how this is
going to develop. Okay, perfect. So you
can see what it's produced. So the
narrative, it's not for creators, rules,
who this is for, who this is not for,
etc., etc. And it's already got a lot of
stuff. So pilot one is on the page. Two
things I'd flag before we move to voice.
What I'm going to do is what we're
against section is too soft. Sharpen it.
So it's done a really good job. What I'm
going to do is this section in
particular, I want it to get sharpened.
And you know, this process here requires
a little bit of back and forth just so
that you're happy with it. But of
course, it can get you somewhere really
quickly. But it's important to read this
and take some time with it. So I'm going
to put this sharpen it. We're not
against AI, etc. So you can see right
here it's recreating it. Now essentially
all you would do is you could put
something like this
and it would be this simple. Then I can
just literally paste this document that
it creates into my brand brain. You can
do skills etc with all of this today.
I'm not going to cover that just to get
the basics done. But if you want me to
dive into coding skills etc. building
something a bit more automatic let me
know in the comments. So I've got this
document. I would literally press
download. Then I'm going to head back to
brand master brain. Put that into there.
And you can see that now that's there.
Now in the same conversation, what you
can do is paste this. So we're building
a pillar to voice referencing the
positioning document. This is a kind of
the pillars all work in cohesion. So
referencing the position document you
just logged in. Make sure that this
voice is consistent with the
positioning. So this is why we're doing
this because I want them to all be
aligned. And I feel like a lot of the
time, you know, when you're separating
things, etc. In this case, it can make
your brand conflict and actually cause
confusion. Remember, we're doing all of
this to be more decisive, to allow our
decision-m once we have this system
built to be quicker, sharper, less
guessing. [music] So again, you can go
back and forth with this, but what I
would do is if there's a particular part
you don't like, change it. Okay? But the
reason again dynamic that we're doing
one at a time and that you can save in
the project because you can shift things
anytime. If there's a visual change, if
there's a change in your voice, etc.,
you can change it.
Okay. So, same thing again. So, I would
press download and then I'm going to
just what you can do is just go back
again and literally throw that in there.
Go back to here. Now, we're going to
start heating this up. So, we're going
to do the visual one, and you're just
going to go through this one. With the
visual one, I'm going to show you
something different as well. We're going
to do this, but then I'm going to
actually get it to create me like a
branding visual. This one's slightly
different than others as well because I
like to have like visual kind of
referencing documents as well which are
visual because it's visual. Okay, so
I've got my glasses on so you know
things are getting serious. So we've
just done the visual one and you can see
that it's given me the brand uh the
document again but for this one it's
also given me this brand board right
here. So if I press that you can see it
pops up. It's given me this brand board
and if I press it it's essentially
creates this kind of board for me which
again is useful for a visual referencing
point. So, it has composition
principles, you know, etc., etc. We did
cover this in the visual brain in a
previous video of mine, but this is more
of an overall one, okay? And you can
change this at any point, you know, you
can use Canva to edit it, etc., using
magic layers. There's so many things you
can do, but this is a useful aspect of
the visual. Once we did the visual, we
then move to the story, which is the
final piece of our pillar, which boom,
we get all of that. Once that's done,
you ask for the dock. Once again, you
get it. Once you get that, then you have
all your four pillars in four different
documents which are dynamic. You can
edit at any point and you just re-upload
them onto your project. Now I asked for
it to confirm the names, summarize each
one at each sentence so that I can make
sure that it's correct what you know
I've done. Tell me what the master brand
can now do that it couldn't before. So
it's given me you know the right
information for each one. What the brain
references from now on, positioning,
voice, visual identity, you know, does
this lead with a direct a declaratory
speak to one person, refuse to hedge,
etc. What the brain can do. Every prompt
started from zero. Every caption had to
be reexlained. Every thumbnail had to be
rebriefed. Every video idea had to be
defended on the spot. The brand was
implicit, held in your head, scattered
across documents, inconsistent across
surfaces. Now I'm able to, you know,
push back on weak directions. Hold
consistency across different surfaces,
translate between layers. It's changed a
lot of things. Give me three YouTube. I
went straight into it. give me three
YouTube concepts for my next YouTube
video and some Instagram content and
boom posting daily killed my content the
enemy it aims at the angle the opener
etc. Obviously you know this is
completely different video you know
content but the point is it's now
referencing this okay and with this you
can use this to do so much in terms of
obviously you can have different
projects which are carousel focused etc
but you can create a master brand
document which you can then take to
other chats but you always want to maybe
cross align you know your final scripts
your final stuff with here just for
alignment just for updates this is how
you have a system so this is your
command center for branding and you can
see everything is on brand right here
again Instagram content each Instagram
post boom posting daily kill my business
you know it's even giving me the kind of
brand guidelines as well and of course
if I wanted to create carousels with
this the exact same thing it's all here
you know to be honest to automate
something as well this makes things so
much easier because then you're
automating your voice positioning
visuals etc okay here is some advice
that I want you to really pay attention
to so most people fill in the identity
and the audience, then write two vague
lines about the voice. Vague rules will
give you generic outputs every time.
Okay? Now, I'm not going to tell you to
go back and write some essays, but spend
a bit of time doing it. And something
that I suggest is sometimes when doing
your prompts, you know, creating brains,
different things like that, just grab a
notepad and pen and step away from the
computer, from the phone, and just write
your ideas. Okay? Spend a few minutes
with your thoughts. take a picture of
it, then add it to your AI and you've
got a whole different kind of real input
to that which will change your second
list and you know the the generic
outputs that will happen. Okay, next
thing is not everything needs to be a
skill. A lot of information online about
Claude, about this, about that is you
can turn this into a skill. You can use
co-work for this, you can do guys, you
know, just keep things simple, okay?
Like in reality, when you're in a
workflow, you're not going to be doing
skill skill uh skill like you know
there's going to be a time and place for
everything. And don't try to just build
this overefficient system because just
by you using AI, just by you
understanding, just by you building
these workflows, you will start to
understand things. Okay? So don't
overengineer, overengineer things. Okay?
A month of content is not a month of
posting. You have 30 pieces sat in front
of you. That does not mean you post 30
times. It means you finally get to
choose what goes out. Something with
social media is, you know, for me
personally, something that I really
disliked about being in the social media
space is a lot of the advice tells you,
you know, post as much as possible. You
know, you need to be posting four times
a day. You need to be posting five times
a day. Like guys, in reality, it's not
like that. Like on my Instagram, for
example, I post like three, four times a
week. And for me, I've realized that
that's sustainable. That's how often I
want to post. And it just works super
well for me. and I'm able to grow that
way. All of this advice, you know,
telling you that you need to post every
day and all like, you know, push
everything to the limit is not true
because there's great creators who post
once a week and they grow tons. Okay?
What we want to focus on is quality.
when we're using AI. So, in this case,
for example, now we're going to be able
to have a range of content and think,
okay, if I'm going to post four times a
week or three times a week and I've got
30 posts, that means I can pick the best
and I'm going to go with those. I'm
going to test. So, you see things
change. These three things will make a
big difference. Okay? So, you have a
claude that knows your brand, which is
extremely important because every social
media profile is essentially a brand,
but you don't have anything made yet.
Well, guess what? We're about to make
something. Some carousels, images, and
videos. Let's get into it. Okay, so now
it's time for us to start building our
system. Now, one of the things with
carousels, which are the swipe posts on
social media, is with image generation
in the past, it's been difficult to get
that consistency from post to post. And
you can see here that I've been able to
build entire post sequences. So you can
see this is you know post one, two, you
can see right here,
three, four, all in the same format. And
if I show you again here, you can see
the same thing. And I've been able to do
that using a particular prompt style
called JSON prompting. And this is an
important aspect of our system. And I
need you to understand. So you can see
here, right here, the prompt style. Now,
let me show you how we're going to do
this. Now, we're going to jump over to
Claude. So I'm using Claude. Claude is
my go-to. Now I'm in my vault. I'm going
to give you the skill so that you can
have your JSON prompt in your Claude at
all times. The exact same thing with
chat GBT. So I'll also add a chat GBT
version in there if you use chat GBT. So
what you want to do to install it is go
to here first. Go to settings and make
sure that you have capabilities that you
have this turned on. The next thing you
want to do is go to customize. Here is
where your skills and connectors live.
What I want you to do here is press plus
then press upload skill. And there you
would drag the file in there and follow
the steps and simply upload it. What
this will do now is any time that you
type, you know, turn this into a JSON
prompt. And you'll see later on in the
system, give turn this into a JSON
prompt um or you know, give me a a
prompt for nano banana for chajd image.
it will automatically to create the
prompt using this as a reference point.
So it will create it in this JSON kind
of way so that your prompts are always
kind of these longer very high
information you know exactly how kind of
AI wants the prompts to be and this is
going to make your life so so much
easier. So I deserve a like and a
subscribe for that. Um but yeah so all
you need to do is follow those steps.
The steps will be in the vault and
you'll be able to do that. Now, we're
going to create this project which is
going to allow us to basically get our
carousels in a matter of seconds. So,
I've already created one an hour ago.
You would literally just press new
project, type in like carousel
generator, whatever. Create the project.
So, I'm going to create it now quickly.
And you can see here, so instructions
plus, and you' paste the instructions
which I will provide in my vault. And
so, let's see here. right here. You can
see all of the instructions are right
there. And now I can show you. So yeah,
that's basically it. And obviously you
can use different models, test it
around. Um, now I'm going to show you
how I've been kind of interacting with
them. So you've seen me create a bunch
of stuff here. So yeah, so let's start
with this one. So what you want to do is
now of course if you give your projects
more about branding, etc. is going to be
better. But for the purpose of this
video, I'm using reference images from
Pinterest, etc. to provide that context.
But if you have like the right branding,
you know, the right examples yourself,
then you can do that for your project.
So if we go here to the motive, let's go
to the Nike one. So for example, what I
did was went over here to Pinterest and
typed in what did I type in like
um let's see what did I type in social
media. social media post. So, social
media post.
And you can see that there's a bunch of
different I was kind of just getting
inspiration and I grabbed this one here.
Now, obviously, you want to be more
specific, you know, or for example, if
you find something on Instagram that you
like, you know, like the design of,
etc., you can grab that. So, for the
purpose of this video, I just grabbed
something from here. And then going back
to here, I put in my hat. So, where is
my hat? So, I have this Jordan hat right
here. And then I was thinking, you know,
what should I make a carousel about? Let
me do a Jordan hat. So I took a picture
of Jordan hat and I want to create a
carousel for my Nike Jordan hat in a
similar visual style to the attached
reference. So these are my two visual
points. The first thing this project
will do is a visual tear down of your
reference. So you can see right here
portrait frames etc etc. Carousel
concept. It will start then designing
this carousel concept. So you can see
hook the only cap you need deep black
background blah blah blah context
heritage middle beat etc. And then it
will say ready for step two say run the
skill to turn these slides into Jason
prompts run the skill and turn these
into etc. Now what you want to do is say
individually. So it did it all in one go
for me. Can you share them with me
individually? And you will start getting
all of these prompts like this. And now
you have a carousel system. And you can
see right here, if I copy this, go to
here. Now, something to pay attention to
on Trabt image 2 is you have different
variations. So, I'm actually just going
to run this. So, we got low, medium, and
high. So, obviously, the higher the
model you use, etc., the more credits
and stuff you're going to use. What I
recommend doing is, you know, if you
want to start testing and stuff, play
around with low and medium so you can
test and get kind of a visual reference
and then you can even go back to Claude
and to, you know, in terms of
resolution, go 1K or 2K. You don't need
to go to 4K for the purpose of this
video. You know, I'm recording a YouTube
video which is seen by a few people. So,
I try to export in, you know, higher
settings. But essentially, then you have
all the aspect ratio. So, if you're
doing a thumbnail, you can do, you know,
21 or 16 this one. Then you have the
different for story it would be 9 by 16.
So you'd have it all here. This batch
size means how many you want to generate
a time. So you can see I always do four
just you know because I want to and want
to see as many as possible. But if you
were limited on choice you know you
could do two one at a time to keep it
really concise. But honestly once like
there's not really much difference
between what I'm generating you know
honestly like look at this one. Once I
have the right system built you know
which we've already started building.
You could literally bring this down to
one. You know, have this on 2K, have
this on low or medium, and your, you
know, generations would cost way less.
So, there are ways to go around this.
And yeah, I just love the feel of using
Hicksfield like this. It's just so much
easier. You know, I just press an image,
for example. I can see my prompt. I can
see the model I used. I can see kind of
the settings. I can press download. I
can, you know, press reference. You
know, I can press upscale enhancer. You
know, there's just so many different
things I can do with this all in one
place and it just makes my life so much
easier. So, let's just generate this
right now. So, 3x4 image 2. And
honestly, it's that simple. And what you
would do is, so I'm going back to here
is you would just copy,
paste, generate. Go back, copy, paste,
generate, and then you would have your
full carousel. Now, of course, there are
going to be ways to automate this, you
know, to make this even smoother.
Although I do think this is pretty
smooth because honestly this once you
have it built it takes a matter of
seconds. Now I did create some other
chats as you can see right here. So to
test things out properly, you can see I
was playing around with some
motivational content. So if I go here
and type in
motivational sports content, you've seen
this all around social media. You know
these kind of like this, like that. And
these are not easy to make, you know,
they take some time. And I really wanted
to experiment with using Chad GBT for
this. And it turns out it did a really
good job. Like if I look at this one
right here, you know, the text looks
clean. And to be honest, I didn't give
it much context. So if I go to
motivational, you know, I put these
three reference images here. I want to
make a carousel with a design inspired
from the attached, which is motivational
carousel. Tell people like I could be
way more specific. I could say
particular font. I could, you know, as I
said, I could give it more brand
references.
And then if I did want to include, you
know, famous people, etc., similar to
how these guys do it, then obviously I'd
have to add the reference images because
it won't just pluck them out of thin
air. But if you want to be more, you
know, not have a particular kind of uh
famous person, you know, then it can
easily generate that for you. And it was
able to do that, you know, as you can
see kind of here, you know, with these
images. And it looks ultra realistic.
So,
but you know this honestly has really
impressed me. You know, there are a few
glitches like this one. You know,
Machamp hands. Um, is it Machamp? Yes,
it is Machamp. And here. Yeah. Well,
just that one really. But you can see
like how good the text comes out. Like
there's tiny bits of overlap here, etc.
And how like honestly how clean does
that look? So, and this is just me
testing for a few hours. Like if I was
to build a whole thing about this,
it would be
crazy. Like you know production value on
social media is super important. You
know in this age of AI where anything is
basically possible when your text when
your carousels are just you know get up
in black and you know it's just so
simple
and you're starting from scratch it's
going to be hard to grow. So this allows
you to be creative and I want you to be
creative. Okay, this was one I had
already kind of created before and you
can see this one here. So, this one I
actually got from an Instagram post and
just referenced it, but I wanted to test
its kind of capabilities with text. Gray
with Alex one out of seven protein
breakfast and it just look it just came
out so clean in terms of composition,
everything like the text,
cottage cheese, peach bowl, etc.
You know, if you have a website, if you
have a book, if you have a YouTube
video, if you have anything you want to
add information to, it can digest that
and turn it into a carousel for you.
I mean, you know, what what more can you
want really? So it's done an incredible
job with the overnight oats jar mega
head fiber richch 25g protein you know
and with this system that we've built
here you know if you go and see you know
love this template okay so this one I
actually asked for it to give me some
ideas so you can see okay closest to the
reference 5minute lunches high protein
snacks under 200 calories one pan
dinners make ahead meal prep you know
seasonal cocktails quick workouts by
body part and then I picked okay and
then it actually asked me which
direction do you want to run with one
pandas as boom and it just started to
build it for me. So slide one, you know,
this is all of that, etc., etc. These
are the slides. And then I would just
simply run this and I get the prompts.
Paste them here and I have my carousel
without needing to, you know, go on to
without needing to go onto, you know,
Canva, paying a designer, anything like
that. Right now it's taken a bit longer
as it's still very early in terms of
it's just been released and I'm probably
doing it on a high setting but it makes
life so so much easier and I think you
know you can see some of the stuff I've
been practicing here you know even
Necrono you know look at how clean and
that kind of glass etc transparency here
you know it's come out amazingly and a
lot of the time before in image
generators it really struggled with that
carousels have been a total game changer
for me over the last few months. And
after obsessing over them, I've been
able to get some insane results. And you
can see right here, 96,000 likes, over
130,000 shares, and you know, I've been
able to build something where it's my
brand. I'm getting tons of messages
about it. And the beauty of all of this
is that this is leveraging the power of
AI. So, I'm able to do these in a matter
of minutes once I have this system set
up. Now, this has taken me tons of time,
tons of work, and after getting so many
messages about this, I've decided to put
this into an engine that you can buy
now. And the link is in the description.
But this is just going through the
website. So, for anyone who is
interested using this method, I've been
able to save a ton of money because I
know longer pay designers, you know, $50
to $100 per carousel, but also a ton of
time because once you install this
system, you literally go to it and it
starts creating those carousels. Now you
can see right here, you know, these are
some of the carousels I've been able to
create. Carousels are the number one
lead generation system that exists out
there in terms of time to lead. Okay,
real long form content is obviously
amazing, but takes way more time. Le
carousels are insane for lead
generation. You can see the amount of
saves that I get. It's it's incredible.
Now, the website will go through
everything you get from a week of
content in under an hour once the system
installed and optimized. Never open a
blank page again. We have an ideation
system which whether you have no idea,
whether you have a old video, whether
you have something else to inspire it,
you can get ideas from virtually
anything or what you already have. You
never write the prompts. It's all set up
because this is my system. A feed that
looks like one brand content nobody can
copy saves that turn into DMs. The full
kind of modules and everything is
available on the website for you to look
at. You know, I want people who are
serious to actually invest into this.
Then you have all the bonus resources
that that you get as well. So 40 plus
written CTAs sorted by goal carousel
breakdowns. This is for those who think
carousels could have a massive impact on
their social media growth business
because this has changed the game for
me. The link is in the description. All
the details are there. This is a
founders price right now. So it will go
up in price in the future. Anyone who's
thinking, "Oh, this is available on
YouTube." It's not because no one gets
results like these using this system.
Plus, you might get snippets here or
there from my videos. But this
particular, it's not a course. It's an
engine. So, by the end, you will be
installing this engine step by step with
me so that you can create this yourself
because this is the same engine that I
use to create my carousels. Uh, any
questions, feel free to reach out on
Instagram. But yeah, the link is in the
description. Do not sleep on carousels.
For us to get B-roll or video AI video
that actually looks good, we need to
actually spend some time building a
system. And the first step of this is
our locking our vibe. Now, when it comes
to video, there are six important
elements that we're going to focus on.
And I'm going to give you a cheat sheet.
You're going to run with me. So, you can
pause the video, download this, and run
through it with me right now. Makes all
the difference. So, light, color grade,
film, stock, lens, movement,
composition. These are not complicated.
I'm about to go through it. Let's look
at light. You're watching a video right
me. You see me in the corner right
there. If I move this, you'll see that
there is less light on. I add more
light. I put the brightness up. It makes
a big difference. I turn the lights off,
etc. Color and grade. How does it look?
Film stock lens. Now, here I've got a
few examples to kind of show you this,
but you can see right here. So, light
direction. Where is it coming from? If
the light was coming from there, this
would look completely different. If it's
hard, soft again it would look
different. Now let's look at this. So
blue hour photography. Okay. So this is
kind of your lighting because the person
is taking these photos in that light. So
blue light you can see what does it look
like? Blue. [laughter]
If I look at golden hour photography
which is just before sunset you can see
it's completely different. And if I put
that into my prompt again it makes a
difference. What we're building is a
lock string here for our prompts. And
you're going to do that with me right
now. Again let's take this further. So
you can see color and grade. We've kind
of gone through that. Colorful is not a
kind of grading or a prompt or
information that actually is useful. If
I go to here, which is a Kodak Portra
400, you can see the style of shots that
you get. And you can see kind of the
consistency around them, the vibe.
Remember, we're building a vibe. Um, and
you can see if I go to nostalgic summer
photography, again, the vibe. If I go to
Mediterranean film aesthetic, again,
it's a different vibe. Okay? Okay. And
you can see how it kind of the the
colors the which ones pop, which ones
don't. This is not too complicated.
Okay. So, texture and film stock, the
strongest single lock. This is a magic
lever. A named stock forces the same
grain contrast every time, which is what
holds a hold library. Okay. So, you can
see here how an example looks string,
which I'm actually going to use in the
video. And I'll show you actually the
difference. If I remove this and add
something else, the difference that will
come out. Now again what I would suggest
you doing is downloading this putting
this into um claude and actually asking
it to go through it with you and give
you suggestions based on you know your
situation but it's worth doing research.
So for example if I like a particular
film so call me by your neighbor
cinematography you can see here the
cinema the photography you know if I go
to this one it's different to to that
right and if I go to this one it's
different because they all have their
independent styles and you can get
inspiration from anywhere to build that
lock for you. Remember, this is based on
these six things and will make all the
difference. Simply download this, fill
it out, and you'll get something like
this. And then you have that locked. But
we're going to take this further to the
next level right now and actually work
with the script to take this to level
two. If you want me to dive deeper into
building your vibe, the visuals, you
know, building a true brand with all of
this kind of for video, again, just let
me know in the comments something about
visuals, vibe, whatever.
Okay. So, this is where we take things
to another level. Okay. And this is
where Claude becomes our brain. So,
consistent is enough. So, we have our
kind of lock vibe. Yeah. But same look,
same shot, but every shot then becomes
the same, right, on video. Like I've
tested it where every shot just looks
good, but then is like literally the
same. So, again, it just makes you fall
asleep. Whereas, if we have the same
look but different shots, different kind
of energy to it, it makes a massive
difference. And this is where we take
the story director and take it to
another level. Now again, this is part
of the freebie. All we need to do is go
down to part two, story director, and
you can see everything right there. But
let's jump into this right now and show
you what this is all about. So what this
does is allows you to change the shot
every time. So rather than a wide rather
than having like every shot just wide
angle, wide angle, wide angle, some are
going to be wide, then suddenly it'll be
close, then suddenly low angle, looking
up, tracking, aerial. This builds a
professional highquality sequence that
will tell your script in a completely
different way and it's not complicated
once you have this locked in. Let's do
that right now for you. So, what you
want to do is once you have your look
string done, so this section right here,
you want to paste your script and then
run this prompt right here. So, paste
your look string, paste the prompt, and
you can save this forever. But what we
want to focus on in this is basically
you have a feeling. Okay? When we're
creating content, we're trying to get
the audience to interact with us or to
feel something they want. And we can do
that through energy. You know, what kind
of energy are we giving off in this
video? Is it is it dark? Is it deep? You
know, because people are going to feel
that way where it's vibrant, you know,
there's different aspects, nostalgia,
etc. It's going to make all the
difference. Again, shot type. All of
this will lead to your prompt. This
makes all the difference. So, you can
see right here, feeling what a viewer
should feel. read under their motion.
So, I've done that exactly right here.
And again, you are my director. I'll
give you my script and my locked visual.
And you can build a skill for this. You
can build a project. Super easy. If you
want to know more about skills, watch
this video right here. But again, you
can see, so I've put my script right
here. The day starts before the noise.
Espresso fast and bitter. The way they
make it here. Then the road that hangs
off the cliffs cliffs all the way down
to the water. And boom. What it starts
to do is then understand, okay, what's
the feeling here? So, at the beginning,
it's anticipation, stillness, energy,
low, shot type, wide, establishing. So,
it's an establishing shot. There's the
prompt. Boom. And it just does that for
every single one. And once you have this
in flow, you have your locked, you have
this, then you can start to generate
content, which is going to make all the
difference. And you can do it in minutes
because you have the two systems or the
complete system to allow you to do that.
Let's jump back into seed dons so you
can see the power of this in action.
Okay, so we've got our prompts right
here. Again, I'll add some extra to the
bottom of this, but you can see there's
pointers and everything right here. But
essentially, we've got this information.
Now, it's time to bring it together and
start creating it for our video. We're
going to generate this in seedance 2.0.
But instead of me doing it right here,
what we're going to do is use the Claude
MCP. So, we can actually connect
Hickfield to Claude, which means that I
don't need to go to this Hickfield right
here. And I could do it all within clude
claude and use any model any time. So
right here you can see I've kind of
prepped this. I'm generating b-roll with
sea dance 2.0 etc etc. I'll share all of
this with you. I've put my prompts and
you can see I've got my content. Okay.
So for the first one I did I went with
the Kodak Portra 400. Now because for
this video I wanted to do a POV angle.
So for example what I mean by point of
view which is I'm the influencer. I'm
traveling sharing a quick kind of uh
information about my trip. But then I
realized, you know, from these clips
that they weren't looking like real
enough. I mean, they look super high
quality, but not real enough, like as in
like an influencer potentially wouldn't
be shooting that, would they? They
wouldn't be rolling around with an 8K
camera. This one looked pretty good. And
you can see seed dance is by no means
like struggling or anything. Like, it
followed my prompt to the tea. And the
quality is immense. Immense like
compared to a few months ago with other
models. Like look at this. It's insane.
But the difference was I removed that
Kodak part and and what I decided to do
was change it to an iPhone. So what I
wanted to do is you know what? I'm
creating a POV for me. So we're going to
change this to an iPhone and keep the
rest the same. And suddenly it was
completely different. So you can see at
the beginning of the video I have this
B-roll of me walking or whatever. You
know, you don't need to use all 8
seconds, but boom, I could use this. It
tells the story. I've got the caption
here. I've just been talking and it
changes. Again, look at this. Just this
image right here looks insanely real and
way better. Again, I can use it for a
few seconds, generate more wherever I
want, but it starts to build this story.
And again, it's all in in kind of this
this flow of color and following my uh
kind of lock. Again, following it. And
you can see here, same thing. Whereas
before, again, it's just too much in
terms of professional. It's got that
lighting. It's got that, you know, vibe.
It looks insane. But for me as an
influencer for POV, it it needs to look
a lot better than that. So you can see
here again, you know, this is way more
realistic. You know, it's it's got kind
of that that drop there for a moment,
you know, and you don't need to use all
six sec like all 8 seconds. I could just
boom, leave that right there. 8 seconds
and it's done. And then that's like a
few seconds. That's probably like 2 3
seconds and it's done. And that's what
adds the vibe to your video. Again, for
the sec the next shot, you could see
potentially I was showing, you know,
people's um table. Um yeah, you know,
but it's but again I was able to
generate this in one go. Okay, like in
one single prompt it was able to
generate all of this and that's the
massive difference here. Again, you can
see, you know, it's it's it's just built
all of them. So I don't think that's
part of it, but you can see the
difference it makes. Like this looks
insanely real. Okay. Um you know, look
at that zoom even right there. Like a
small like real kind of live zoom. And
this looks incredible how real that
looks. like when 2.5 comes out, I'm
definitely making a video because if it
gets better than this, I don't know how.
But you can see, look at that. Insane.
Um, and you know, for me as an
influencer, if I was struggling to, for
example, you know, I had a deal with a
company or something and I wanted to,
you know, and I was missing some good
shots. Boom. I can grab the shots right
now. If I was a motivational speaker, if
I was a nutritionist, it doesn't matter
who I am. I can now get content that
actually matches my video, tells a story
is unique and I can build it in a matter
of seconds once you have the system in
place and Hicksfield is able to generate
this all within Claude using the MCP.
So, this is an absolute game changer.
The link is in my description because
again, when a new model comes out, we
want to test it. We want to use that for
our B-roll and again we'll have access
to it immediately instead of having all
of these different ones to sign up to.
Now, let's say you were using yourself
for this. So, for example, if you wanted
to add yourself in your B-roll, how
would you do that? Well, let me know in
the comments if you want me to create
one where you actually use people in the
video or like even yourself because that
is a bit harder, but I can definitely do
that as a follow-up. Okay, so you have
work that looks like yours, but you
don't have a way to stop repeating
yourself. So, now it's time to teach it
a job once and never explain it again.
Now, how to activate a skill. So, let's
say I have a script for a video. Okay.
Now, we know how important hooks are.
Typically, let's say that there are six
different different variations of hooks.
Of course, I can make a whole video
about hooks, but let's say there are six
variations. So, contrarian,
patent interrupt, identity call out,
curiosity gap, etc. Stat shock, you
know. But what we want to do is I've got
my script here. Here's a video on that
script. I need to, you know, brainstorm
some more hooks quickly. Now, I'm going
to just put in hooks. And boom. It
already knows my hook style, you know,
the way I've told it to, you know,
create hooks, what I'm looking for. So,
I don't need to do much apart from put
slash and hook. Now, of course, the
beauty of this is that I could do this
in any chat. So, I could be in another
chat, which I'm about to show you later,
which is kind of my video chat. Once
I've done the videos, etc., I could be
like, "Okay, let's just work on the
hooks now." and I just go boom and it
starts to create hooks based on what I'm
working with. So essentially instead of
me thinking about prompts and having
these prompts saved everywhere, I have
it saved in my skills folder. Now you
can see right here, boom, it's given me
10 different hooks immediately. Best
fits the script six and nine. So one
claude feature cut my content week from
50 hours to 20 statshock. Boom. And
that's how simple it can be. Now in
terms of how to install it, it's so
easy. All you do is go to customize on
your tab and it will bring up this. You
go to plus right here and you can see
you can browse skills. So other skills
or you can create skills. You can write
skill instructions or upload a skill or
create with claude. Of course, normally
I do write skill instructions and then
put you know as I mentioned the kind of
format right here. What you can also do
is and I will it will be in my vault is
the skills that I've created. I will
give them to you all and you can just
drag them in here and then you have the
skill right there. So skills are super
easy to create. Let's jump over to the
next skill because this is where things
the magic starts to happen.
Okay, now this is where things start to
get spicy. And so now I'm about to show
you how to do it with images and video.
And this is where things really take go
up to another level. So you can see
right here, this is my image generation
skill. And in this chat right here is
where I have it. So you know, as again,
I've made new chats for to kind of
showcase these skills. But normally,
let's say I've been, you know, have a a
complex chat or a chat with multiple
different scripts, different things. A
skill is going to just quickly come in
and do the task it needs to do. In this
case, I've put a script here for a page
I have. And then I've put my prompt,
right? Or my skill beats image. Boom.
And essentially, it understands my
branding already because that's kind of
built into the skill. But you and you
can easily edit this. So, for example,
what you would do is, you know, just
edit it. But before we jump into that, I
want to show you something. So you can
see that I've been able to generate
these images within Claude using Chad
GBT image too. And that's because
Hicksfield have just released this MC
Higfield MCP, which allows you to
connect Hicksfield to Claude, Plexity,
etc. And it's a total game changer
because I don't need to go from
Hicksfield to Claude prompt to
Hicksfield. Instead, I'm doing it all in
one chat and it literally saves at least
50% of your time and it's so easy to do
once you have Higsfield. Link will be in
the description. All you do is go to
settings, connectors, press add custom
connector, and the instructions are
right here. So, OpenClord settings, add
custom connector, connector, sign in,
and literally you have it in the chat.
And you can see right here how it works.
So, I've put in my script, and then I've
put B image, and it's come up with six
or seven different kind of images. Now,
the reason you would use this is, you
know, it's super important to use images
for B-roll, you know, to help explain,
you know, once you're creating a real,
you know, let's say you're in the
educational space for gardening, you
know, you want to suddenly pop up a, you
know, dandelion or something, I don't
know, like you could just create that in
a matter of seconds from your script on,
you know, Claude using Hicksfield. You
know, this is super useful. It just
makes life easier. We know content
creation is not easy, so why not try to
make it a bit easier? So, and you can
see for the videos which I'm about to
show you, it's very similar. So, going
back to here, let's see what's actually
created. And this the beauty of this is
all created with one singular prompt.
And it's come out really good. So, this
is more of a kind of stoic theme
clean using chat GBT chat GBT image 2
right here. Now with the skills at any
time you can just go to your im your
skill and let's say you know so I've got
some specific things in here like for
example you need to use hickfield image
2 when you're creating the images but
let's say nano banana 50 comes out all
you would do is go here and change this
to nanobanana 20 you know whatever you
make those changes and the skill gets
updated and the workflow remains the
same it remains super you know good with
here I've put some branding details just
for the purpose of this video, but
again, if you had more branding visuals,
etc., you'd put them all here and it
would be there forever. So, it makes
your workflow for this specific use case
so so useful. And again, this is all
saved to Higsfield. So, you can see the
images are all here. You know, if you
don't need to come here, honestly, I
barely come here now. I've just been
using it in MC in in Claude. But, you
know, it's all here if you wanted to
play around with it now. And obviously,
if you wanted to do low quality size,
etc., You can do that all within Claude.
Now, of course, this can all be
automated, which takes us to another
thing as well. If you want me to make a
video about automation, you know, trying
to do even more with this, let me know
in the comments. Now, what do we do to
take this even further? That would be to
do videos as well. So, with videos, you
know, again, hero moments, great for
personal brands, YouTubers, businesses.
You could do this with motion graphics,
you could do this with anything. And
again, I put the same um prompt that I
put here, but what I did was I wanted it
to do the images first using my image
kind of generation skill and then do the
video generation skill, which I'm again
going to show you right here very
quickly. Again, very similar. Um then I
go to here and let's see what it's
actually come up with. So it did all the
images.
Boom, boom, boom. Then I thought, you
know, let me try something a bit more
fast-paced. So we did the images again
again again and let's scroll down and
have a look. So you can see right here
these are the videos. So
like
wow you know one of the things as well
this is actually really good at
prompting. So this like having
hicksfield within Claude also makes your
prompting that much better as well. Um
look at that. And then you know
obviously I can take this further start
adding text etc. And you can do some
auto editing as well. Again if you want
that you know taking v if you want me to
make more videos about like videos using
claude etc. Again let me know. But
essentially look I have a whole sequence
of videos from one singular prompt. You
can see once I did the images it auto
started to do the videos again all here
and all super useful. There's no excuses
to like not make content. That's good.
Again, if you're in a situation where
you were making a YouTube video and you
wanted to make a few, you know, images
for it, it could be the same. Obviously,
you'd make a change, you know, where
this would be 16 by9, it'd be designed
for YouTube, etc. You know, it might be
slightly longer in duration. And you
just make those edits. It's honestly
that simple.
Okay, so this next one or next two is
honestly my favorite and the biggest
wow. So, you can see over the last few
months on my YouTube channel, I've
changed my branding, the way I do
thumbnails. I now make themelves and
it's working really well for me. Now,
look at this. So, I've been able to
create a skill for my thumbnail. So,
I've been a So, essentially what I did
here was I grabbed my four, you know,
one of four of my latest thumbnails,
which have performed pretty well. And
you could do this for basically anything
for this particular skill right here.
And let's say I've got a video idea. So,
you know, video idea experiment I'm
thinking is doing like how to create 30
days of content in like 30 minutes using
just a claw chat. And just with this
skill and my idea right here or with the
title, it's able to do do a style
profile in terms of like colors,
typography, you know, etc., etc. Then
it's able to like, you know, identify
that we need like keywords or whatever
in the in the in the thumbnail. So, you
know, it wants it wants to go with 30
days. From there I say 30 days is good
and it will generate a thumbnail for
this title based on these. So let's have
a look. And with that it generated this
30 days
face it created new carousels or new
images. Okay. So you can see here
doesn't let me. [snorts] You can see
here
all these images, none are the like the
one I've just kind of shown you. Yeah,
it's created its own carousel images
here. Now, obviously, there is an issue
potentially here with the shoulder, but
having it in front isn't the worst
thing. 30 days, etc. IG logo right
there. All because of me using a skill.
So, look at how much time and I used to
pay $200 per thumbnail. Damn. Now,
generating now, same beat is 5 minutes,
two prompts, etc. Now the next one is
the face lock. When you're creating
content which you know potentially has
your face or a human face with AI there
can be issues with you know the
generation. So luckily for me you know
I've been doing this for a while my
prompting and you know my systems are
built so it doesn't really happen. Um
but it could happen where you do this
and then suddenly you look like you're a
rhino or a lion or someone completely
different. And I built a skill and this
is where I'm also showing you how skills
can stack on top of each other where I
do a face lock. So for example, if I
wanted it to regenerate but this time
for it to make sure that the face is
locked and essentially this one you can
see just preserves my image at the
maximum capability. So it understands
that it cannot change this and it needs
to redo the thumbnail. So you can see
here rerunning with identity
preservation language injected. So a
higher amount of identity preservation
language into the prompt into this
generation and then boom it comes out
even better. So in this case it actually
recreated some of the carousels and even
added me or a part of me to one of them.
So you can see there there you know so
and it looks super clean. Even changed
this logo etc as well. So, you know,
simply from me doing that, you know,
literally two skills, I'm able to create
a new thumbnail for a YouTube video in a
matter of minutes. Like, this is
unbelievable. And again, you know, if I
wanted to add further skills where I add
variations of, you know, my t-shirt, I
could do that. So, then I would be like,
you know, slashvariations. So, on
YouTube, you can have ABC testing of
thumbnails. So, for example, if I have a
final thumbnail here, I'm happy with
this. You know what? Let's do some
variations where 30 is in orange,
yellow, different colors, you know,
whatever you build around your kind of
flow.
Okay, so before we get to should you
build it and how to build it, let's look
at my final one, which is a caption
skill. Now, this is a super interesting
or simple one, but essentially this
builds my captions for me. And you can
see right here it's built my caption
with already knowing that it has to do
like a um many chat kind of message to
kind of have for the automations. This
again is super useful because if I'm
doing a flow where I'm creating content
and you know suddenly I'm like oh damn I
need a caption. I can just go to you
know IG captions and it will create the
caption based on how I've built it. So
if I scroll down you can see right here
the caption is built in the way that I
want. Um, so this is super useful, okay?
Because I can literally do anything. Be
in any chat. You know, suddenly if I
want to make a quick Instagram video, I
could just put in my idea, which is like
this. You know, this one wasn't
necessarily for me, but and I get the
caption. So again, you know, this is
just super useful. Now, should you build
a skill? You might be wondering. And for
what? Well, let me answer that. So this
is important when you have a recurring
task. So when you have a task that you
know you do pretty often on claude this
is when you should think okay I need a
skill for this you know if it's
structured it has a fixed shape every
time same input same type you know if it
can be handed off so if it's you know
suddenly go and cook me dinner you can't
do a skill for that but if it's
something that you can give to Claude to
just quickly boom and save that's worth
doing so if it's recurring structuring
structured it makes a massive difference
you know if it passes All three of these
you can build a skill passes one or two.
I would say keep it as a prompt. You
need to really be able to, you know,
yeah, don't build skills for one-off
creative writing task where each input
changes the output entirely. Tasks with
no clear output format. Okay? So, for
example, you know, let's say um you
know, for these videos, like I have a
specific style of content that I'm
making for this page. you know the the
the difference is going to be each time
it will be like a different scene
different topics but ultimately the
output is going to be a similar format
the branding etc etc and it's video so
when things are like that recurring it's
worth doing a skill and you can have
loads of different skills so where do
you start let's say you were doing a
personal brand you could have a hook
generator caption writer in your voice
comment reply drafter YouTube titles
thumbnails description chapter writer
course creator lesson outline builder
email sequence you're after sales page
writer business client on boarding
proposal template brand tone checkup for
delegated work what to avoid vague
descriptions asking for confirmation
trying to do too much remember don't try
to do too much with these because you
can stack them okay now if you want me
to make another video about skills where
I go even deeper into them actually
building them you know some more let me
know because I know skills are super
important and for me I'm actively using
them more and more okay you do not want
to sleep on skills. Even if you have
just a few, it's worth doing, okay?
Because it's all about efficiency. For
us as creators or on social media, our
focus or output needs to be on
creativity. Okay? So the tasks which are
repetitive, which we've been creative
once built a system for, those can be
turned into skills because Claude
understands and can repeat that over and
over again. Your effort needs to be more
an ideation or things that require kind
of this fresh creative burst. This is
how you do skills for social media or
for content creators.
Before I show you these 17 unmissable
skills, we're going to start off with me
giving you the rundown. So, skills are
reusable tools that save you hours every
single week. By the end of this video,
you will know how to build skills, how
to use my skills, and it will change
your entire workflow. So you build it
once, you set it up in minutes and it
runs forever and it's triggered forever.
So one word and it will trigger and
start and it's literally saved me so
much time. Now to install skills is
super simple. You go here to your Claude
customize, press skills and then you
have three different options. So you can
browse skills, you can create with
Claude, write skill instructions or
upload skills. So the skills I give you
which will be available in my vault in
the description of this video for free.
I deserve a like. You just literally
come here, drag the file into uploaded
skill and it's ready to go. You're going
to see how skills connect within chats
to build these systems that make my life
so much easier as a content creator.
Let's jump into it. Okay, now I've split
this video up into four sections. So, we
have the universal section which are
universal skills for any content
creator, social media people. Then we
have some which are specific to
Instagram, to YouTube, and then to
building systems and bonuses. So trust
me, you do not want to miss this as you
will learn how you can create them
yourself, how they actually work in a
system and you will be prompted. So this
will trigger your mind to start
thinking, you know what, I could create
a skill for this in your workflow, a
skill for this, changing your life.
This is Jordan Rivera. Now, they are a
fitness coach. They're in this specific
niche. They have this audience. They
have this goal of 300 paid members, £49
a month. coaching app this quarter, etc.
So, I've created this profile of this
creator, this social media account, just
so that we can have this consistency
throughout the video. And you can see as
I built this system, but it doesn't
matter if you're faceless, personal,
brand, business, whatever. This is all
going to be applicable to you. I'm just
having this specific person so that we
have consistency and you can see it in
action. Now, let's jump to Universal
section one.
Okay, so now we're going to start with
the universal skills and these are
extremely important. The first one is
the goal lock. So locks one golem runs
everything you make through it. So
whenever you start a session of shiny
new ideas, this is going to keep you on
track. Let me give you an example right
here. So you can see here I've got my
goal lock and based on Jordan, I've
created this primary goal. So the first
thing you would do with this skill once
installed is goal lock and then put in
your kind of goal. So primary goal, what
who I want to attract, my positioning,
etc. It doesn't need to be like this.
Everything is in my vault, but you could
just literally put any goal. So if your
goal is to get 10,000 followers, you
know, I want to attract this type of
clientele, whatever, put that in, lock
it, and it will say goal is locked and
set. So you can see that it's kind of
done that. Then what will happen is in
any chat going forward, if I have an
idea, you know, with social media,
there's basically endless ideas, shiny
object syndrome. Should I do this? let
me think of this, let me try this. So
anytime you have anything in any chat or
you suddenly start d you know going in a
different path, you can just literally
go go lock and it will double check
whether this idea or the path you're
going down actually matches the goal
that you've set right there. So for
example, I want to make a trending reel
on 75 hard challenge. It's blowing up
right now. Everyone's doing it. Boom.
Goal check 300 paid members by the end
of the quarter. What you brought this is
it on goal? No, because the topic is one
flip but the topic is one flip away from
a strong yes. So what it will do is
actually tell you that you know the
views aren't the goal but it can also
give you a fix on how to make it more
worthwhile to actually get to this
point. So this is extremely important.
You know I run this in any chat that I
have where I'm suddenly going off track
or something like that and boom it will
help me realign my vision. This is an
this is an extremely important one to
use when using AI. No matter who you
are, hooks, hooks, hooks. Everyone is
always talking about hooks. But let me
introduce you to something. There is
something called the climax. A climax is
when you're watching a movie and the
superhero kills the villain. That's the
climax of the whole movie. The movie,
the way the movie has been built up to
that moment. And content is basically
like that. When you have an audience,
they're watching your content expecting
that climactic moment, the wow moment.
Hooks are basically this forced, you
know, controversial statement at the
start that actually don't do anything.
And if you start to understand that your
climax is the most important part of
your newsletter, YouTube video,
everything, it will change everything.
Now, I'm here on my bridge skill. And
for example, what I would do for Jordan,
I've got a random script here, draft.
Okay, I would run this skill and what it
does is basically it instantly
identifies the climax for me and then
then and then it gives me openings which
match that climax. Instead of me finding
these 50 power words to use for hooks,
I'm using the climax. And this is the
best way to create content and stuff
that people just don't talk about when
it comes to social media. And honestly,
if you can understand this, this is
literally one of the most important
things in this video. If you want me to
dive more into reconstructing reals,
carousels, and actually building towards
a climax, let me know in the comments.
But honestly, this bridge can be used
anywhere. So, if I'm creating any piece
of content, newsletter, YouTube video,
Tik Tok, whatever, this bridge is going
to help me create real content which
actually has a real payoff for viewers.
Next, we have the signal mine. So, this
finds content angles hiding in raw data.
So for example, if I have news, Reddit
posts, you know, whatever it is, this
will turn it into actual angles for me
as a content creator. Now, this is an
automation I ran where it was able to
gather information from Reddit X, etc.
And I do this on a daily basis for my
personal brand, etc. If you want me to
make a video about automations, for
research, for analysis, let me know. But
let's say I've got this information
here, and again, remember, you can just
paste blogs, you can put anything. I run
my signal m from this. What it will do
is give me opportunities or or possible
angles for content. So the signals worth
posting about ranked. So the first one
is the 10k steps number was always fake.
Posting on walks are the real lever. The
gym already budgeted for your quitting
by February, etc., etc. Then it just
gives me angles and gets me going in
terms of what I could possibly do for
content. You know, sometimes we're stuck
with content. You know, not sure what to
do. I have this automated where it gives
me information. It saves me time from
scrolling and just wasting a bunch of
time. And this signal mind skill can be
used on anything. So if I had a blog, if
I had a Reddit post, any information, I
just throw it in here, run this, and
it's done. And of course, you can have
an automation system behind. Let me know
in the comments if you want me to jump
more into this, but this is an extremely
useful one to have. Next up is one of my
favorite. Now, often as creators on
social media, we don't actually give our
own stories or stories that are real
life around us. And storytelling is one
of the best ways to build authority.
This pulls the content angles hidden in
pulls the content angles hidden inside
your own stories. So let's say when you
use it, you have a great client win or a
personal moment but only see one post in
it or you can't see a post. So what you
would do for this is so for example, I'd
run my story mode. So mine this for
content. Then you literally type in the
kind of the story. It could be anything.
And what it will do is then tell you
what's in here and the different angles
that you could create for content. And
this is super super important because
honestly your stories, everyone's
stories, it doesn't matter what world
you live in are all unique and position
you differently from everyone else. And
one of the things with content is that
it's all very similar and if you can
stand out, that's your opportunity. Do
not sleep on story mine. It's extremely
valuable. If you want me to dive more
into storytelling, which is a massive,
massive skill, let me know. The next one
is freebie suggest. Now, freebies are a
massive tool if you want to build lead
magnets, if you want to build emails,
you know, if you want to make a
business. Massive. Turns a content topic
into a specific lead magnet graded on
effort versus payoff. So, let me show
you how this would work. So, I would run
my skill right here. I'm making content
this week about so for example if I had
a big chat which was me creating real
content like or ideas for YouTube etc. I
could run my freebie suggest in there b
and ask it to based on this these
content give me some freebies but in
this case I'm just going to run you know
an example piece of content and from
that it's able to give me five different
kind of angles or four in this case
angles of simple freebies that I could
create. So a short PDF, carousel as PDF,
what's in it, what to do on the days the
plan falls apart, you know, and it just
gives me these options which I can then
easily create. Freebies are a massive,
massive tool for me and for most
creators who are leveraging, now is the
best time to do this. And you can see it
always gives me a quick win. So the one
that I could probably do the easiest and
the quickest, boom, done. The keyword if
I want to integrate it into my man many
chat or my automations, it's already
right there. So, it does a lot of the
heavy lifting for me in a matter of
seconds.
Okay, now some of you are here
specifically for Instagram. Let's jump
into the Instagram section. So, here we
have four specific skills. Now, of
course, most of these skills are
interchangeable with different social
media platforms. Caption plus CTA writes
the caption and roots the CTA to the
right mechanism per platform. So, here I
have my example. So caption and CTA
skill write captions for a real I'm
posting about etc. Now for these I'm
kind of just giving a kind of generic
prompt but let's say I'm doing a real.
So, similar to what I've just done in
the previous skill, I've got a real,
then I do my freebie, then I could do my
caption and CTA, and boom, in a simple
uh kind of chat, I've got a sequence.
Create the reel, create the freebie or
the suggest, and create the caption. And
boom, it's able to give me a
professional Instagram caption. And, you
know, in this case, it gives me a
LinkedIn one, etc. Obviously, you can
ask it not to do LinkedIn, not to do X,
etc. And it gives me the CTA kind of
mechanism. So what's going to be kind of
the comment walk exactly the same as the
other one. Keep the caption collapse
friendly etc. Of course if I want you
know these m dashes to be removed in my
um captions you know you just kind of
tweak the skill slightly very simple
tweaking but a very very useful skill a
fundamental basic skill that again is
going to change your chats. Next is the
real scriptor. You guessed it it
couldn't be a video without this. So,
write the full short form script, climax
lead opener, tight beats, visual cues,
batching day. You know, this is super
useful. Of course, you know, I've got
the real script that I'm giving you is
kind of one I've created. But of course,
over time, you want to tweak it, you
know, make it understand your script
style, understand your, you know, your
climax opportunities, the way you create
content. Small tweaks over time. That's
how you're going to create your skill.
Boom. Real scriptor. Write me a real
script on why walking 20 minutes after
meals, you know, and it just starts
creating. And then from there, it's got
the opener beat one. It even gives me
visuals if I wanted to update it and
say, "Don't give me visuals. I don't
need this. I just need text." It does
all of that. But it's super super
simple. Even includes a CTA if that's my
content. Couple of notes. Now, this is
where it gets interesting. So, let's say
I've got my real script. And this is
where I want to start showing you how a
system in this actually works. So, this
already understands want me to run this
opener through the bridge. So, it's
giving me this script, but it
understands that this is how a system
works is boom, let's run it through the
bridge. It understands that and then it
will start giving me better openings
that match the climax of the video. And
there you have it. And then from there,
you know, it would could go on to, you
know, my caption CTA, could go on to my
freebie. And this is how you start
building these systems where instead of
me typing, you know, speaking, all of
this, it's already predetermined or
preset because I've put in the work.
Next up is audience gaps. This is
extremely important because often as
creators or on social media, we focus
very much on, you know, what we're
creating, what I think, what, you know,
all about me. But we need to actually
understand that it's the audience that's
going to watch our video, that's going
to buy something, that's going to like
it, that's going to save it, that's
going to share it. So what does this do?
It surfaces the three questions your
audience is silently asking and what to
possibly do with each. So before posting
to catch what's missing. So this is
extremely important. So here's a real
script I'm about to post. What are the
questions my audience might be silently,
you know, asking when they watch. So So
in this case, you know, this information
might be useful for me to answer in the
caption. So if there's something I've
missed in my reel, I can then focus my
caption to have this information. If I
did this with a real script before I've
recorded it, it might give me a
different outlook on how to readjust my
script. So, you can see here audience
gaps 20-minute walk after dinner. Boom.
What I what if I can't walk after
eating, you know, etc. Yeah. So, the
content is about walking after dinner.
And then it's like, you know, what if I
can't walk after dinner? I'm back on
calls picking up kids. It's dark and
freezing outside. It starts giving you
different perspectives or what people
might ask. And this is honestly a big
big gap. This one is one of my favorite.
Okay. And I didn't do it justice with
the name followup engine. So let's say
one of your posts went viral. What you
would do is start again. Maybe I don't
know what to do. Let's just post this.
No, no, no, no, no, no. What you need to
do is you need to post a follow-up of
that content that's actually going to
match potentially the previous one that
did well. And this does exactly that. So
here follow up engine my reel on walking
20 minutes after meals just blew up
340,000 views 1,200 saves actually would
probably have more saves but there's the
point what it will do why it worked. So
it give you a quick insight into why it
worked and then the follow-up the deeper
cut why timings work. The next question
does it have to be 20 minutes after
every meal. Different angles that you
can follow up. This is how momentum
works on social media. If you understand
this big big opportunity for you to
grow. If you want me to dive deeper into
this I don't know what I'd call this but
you know let's say follow-up like the
follow-up method. Understanding this is
something that people don't speak about
but is one of the key key aspects of
growth on social media.
It's YouTube time. Now, YouTube is where
things get spicy. Again, if you're not
doing YouTube, don't worry because trust
me, there's still opportunities here for
you. And later on in the video, they get
even better. So, YouTube ideation. So,
video ideas built for how YouTube
actually surfaces content. So, when you
use it, you can for planning content.
So, let's actually put this into
practice. So, YouTube ideation. Give me
a YouTube video ideas for my channel. I
help busy professionals 3 to 32 to 45
lose weight substantially without
leaving in the gym etc etc. So what it
will do is then start to give me ideas.
Now again if I'm running the signal mine
I could give the information it gives me
you know from there into this you know
and that's when you start piecing these
skills together but obviously I've kind
of given it a generic one but it then
starts to give me these important pieces
of information. You know what intent is
this search? you know why it gets
discovered because people are actually
potentially typing this you know intent
browse. So people are potentially
browsing and they might be you know is
it's going to stop the scroll. It's
clickbait. Extremely useful to have this
skill when you're ideating because
ideiating is not easy. Okay coming up
with ideas is not easy. But if you're
using the goal one if you're using the
signal mind you're using this one
YouTube content can become easier for
you. YouTube packaging. Now this is a
big one. title and thumbnail word pairs
that never echo each other. So this is
super important. You know, this is
essentially like with packaging, you
know, everyone will have their kind of
own ideas or their own ways to do
packaging. But essentially once you have
like a packaging formula, you've been
testing it. You know, let's say I've got
my idea done. I've got my script done
then or before even I've done that, I
could just do my packaging. Packaging is
super important when it comes to YouTube
because without a good title, without a
good thumbnail, no one is going to watch
your video. You can have the best video
on the planet, but if those two don't
work, you don't understand how people
are going to press your video, then it's
all pointless. YouTube packaging, once
you have a formula, having this in a
skill that you could just go boom
quickly is extremely useful because you
don't want to waste. YouTube videos are
difficult to create. There's so many
different components that being able to
just quickly run through them, get
information fast is going to help you a
ton. This is an extremely important
tool. If you want me to make a video
more about packaging, even for social
media in general, because packaging is
what makes people press a video and if
you understand that, again, it's going
to give you so much better results.
Okay, so one of the first things, you
know, once you have your packaging, once
you've done your signal mind, once
you've got your ideas locked in, what
you want to do is not go straight to
script. Okay, you need to turn a topic
into a full kind of retention awareness
video structure. Okay, so once you have
the stuff logged in, what you want to do
is start outlining how the video could
potentially be. This is extremely
important because a lot of people go
straight into now write me a script, but
you need to have a flow through your
videos. One thing that what you know I
really work on in my YouTube videos is
the flow. So at the beginning of this
video I had the universal part, then I
have the Instagram, then I have the
YouTube, then I have the systems. Like
I'm purposefully building my videos in
that way. You know, if I'd put YouTube
right at the beginning, maybe some of
you would press off the video. So
everything is intentional when you're
creating content. And this helps you to
do that. You could do the exact same for
short form. So when you have an idea,
you know, how am I going to, you know,
structure this? How what's the outline?
An outline is going to give you the the
skeleton. Okay? And having a skeleton is
extremely important. Now, you might be
thinking, you know, this is so many
different steps. But once you have a
skill set up, once it's just a matter
of, okay, skeleton, okay, have a read.
You know, maybe I'm going to swap this
or this doesn't make sense. Done. Next
script, and it just starts to piece
together. So, yes, it seems long, but
those are the steps it takes to achieve
the results that you know people
achieve. This is one of the classics,
long too short. You have a long YouTube
video from a competitor, from a random
channel, from your own. You want to take
it into turn it into some short form
script. Well, guess what? This skill
does exactly that. So, you know, often
you want, you know, often as a creator,
so so, so as I've just said, you might
be in loads of different scenarios. You
might be just researching on YouTube,
looking at other creators. You're not a
YouTube creator, but you can get their
transcript. You have just done a YouTube
video. You want to turn it into some
reals. Boom. All you would do is log to
log to short, put in your script. You
know, in this case, I've just put in a
summary. Summary also works, but the
more information the better. And what it
will do is start then giving you ideas
for your short form content. extremely
useful because once you have this
system, let's say for me, I've got a a
YouTube video and you know, I want to
get people from Instagram to watch my
YouTube video or people to watch my
Instagram for my YouTube, you know, once
you have these systems all tied in and
you're not creating random content for
this, random content for that and it's
all tied together. Things work but much
better for you. Again, this is part of a
bigger system. You can do the opposite
of this as well, short to long. If you
have success on Instagram, you want to
start creating some long form. You know,
where can I find opportunities in my
short form? But ultimately, this is one
of the most popular ones where you have
long YouTube scripts or long pieces of
content. It could even be blogs,
newsletters, anything. And it just is
able to translate that or recreate that
into short form content. This one is a
very popular one. Game changer.
And now we've reached systems. Okay, so
systems are super important. This one, I
think I've maybe said it twice, but this
one is also one of my favorite series.
huge series, Instagram, Tik Tok,
anywhere, series are super important
because people ultimately will watch
multiple pieces of content. Okay? If one
of your videos is about a penguin
falling off a cliff or story about that,
the next one is why you know you need to
grow tomatoes in your garden, then
there's a bit of a kind of no connection
between them. Series make sure that
people keep watching your content, that
they understand what you're posting
about. turns one big idea into connected
multi-part series across cross across
platforms. So right here I've got my
plan a content series around my core
philosophy sustainable fat loss for busy
professional beats every extreme diet.
Now of course this one is kind of a
broader or you know more first step. So
I just wanted to plan a series but let's
say I've currently you know got content
that's performed really well and I
wanted to run the follow-up one. I could
also run a series planner where both of
them work together or in sig and a
series is so useful. So you can see
right here core philosophy why busy
professionals fail every diet the four
levers that actually move fat loss when
you're time poor. So once you have your
ideas, whether it's signal mine or
whatever, run it through a series
planner and that's how you just get
months and months worth of content so so
easily that actually has substantial
value to your audience and is going to
help you build momentum and grow. This
is an absolute important tool. Doesn't
matter if you're YouTube, Instagram,
whatever. Even gives you suggestions,
but of course it's down to you. This is
a big one. So newsletter drafter. So
email marketing is absolutely huge
because essentially with your YouTube,
with your Instagram, with your Tik Tok,
with your ex account, with your
LinkedIn, you don't really own your
audience. But once you start getting
people's emails, you start emailing
them, you own that email list. And this
is a massive valuable asset. And but
creating newsletters, creating emails is
not easy. Okay? But you can actually
create a newsletter drafter that makes
your life easier. Okay? And what you
would do for this is this. So
essentially write a newsletter issue
from my list topic why walking 20
minutes after meals beats chasing 10,000
steps and what that teaches about
sustainable fat loss generally and from
there it will start to build that for
you. Now of course what I would suggest
for this is potentially getting some
formats or some examples of newsletters
in your niche that you like just so that
you can make tweaks to this actual
skill. If you want me to make a video
which goes more into newsletters, lead
magnets, building that system for, you
know, creating an actual business, let
me know because this is a massive aspect
of social media. You know, everyone's
talking about views, you know, growth,
etc. Hooks, hooks, hooks. But what's
that for? It's for this. It's for
building a business. So, if you want me
to speak more about this, let me know.
But again, this is a massive, massive
tool that you do not want to lose out
on. Before I show you these 17
unmissable skills, we're going to start
off with me giving you the rundown. So,
skills are reusable tools that save you
hours every single week. By the end of
this video, you will know how to build
skills, how to use my skills, and it
will change your entire workflow. So,
you build it once, you set it up in
minutes, and it runs forever, and it's
triggered forever. So, one word, and it
will trigger and start, and it's
literally saved me so much time. Now, to
install skills, it's super simple. You
go here to your claude customize, press
skills and then you have three different
options. So you can browse skills, you
can create with claude, write skill
instructions or upload skills. So the
skills I give you which will be
available in my vault in the description
of this video for free. I deserve a
like. You just literally come here, drag
the file into upload a skill and it's
ready to go. You're going to see how
skills connect within chats to build
these systems that make my life so much
easier as a content creator. Let's jump
into it. Okay, so now we have the skill
opportunity finder. So these next two
are so important. These are the meta
skills that literally everyone has to be
using. Okay? And this is where you're
going to be able to build your own. So
essentially for this, it's simple. Here
I have my chat and essentially I've put
in the purpose of this is basically we
all spend a lot of time on claude on you
know doing stuff having these chats
within that we're feeding it
information. We're you know doing stuff
with this skill opportunity finder. What
it does is it will scan all of your
clawed chats and find patterns that you
often repeat that you should have skills
for. So all of the skills I've provided
in this video you can use, but there's
going to be skills that I can't provide
for you that are easily turned into
skills. And this will literally do that
for you. So here you can see on my dummy
account it will it digs into my actual
chat history find the patterns and then
it starts to scan everything and gives
me opportunities ranked by leverage
where it thinks I should have certain
skills you know for my workflow and this
is going to be an absolute this is
probably the biggest game changer now in
this whole video because if you use
Claude for even a few hours a week
there's going to be tons of data and
things you can do to build a better
system. Then the next one is builder,
which is building that skill. You might
be thinking, Alex, but how am I going to
build that skill? Well, guess what?
Claude actually have their own skill
builder provided for all of us. And you
can see right here after that, I was
like/skiller, build me the skill for a
specific one that I wanted. And
literally from there, it gave me
everything. And I would literally, it
literally builds me the skill. And then
I save skill. And then in the future
when I want to run it, I literally go
campaign. I didn't install it in that
case, but it would be like that. And you
can see again that will be in your
personal skills right here. Skill
creator added by anthropic right there.
These two skills alone will change your
entire workflow. Okay? So, you have a
brain, a generator, and a set of skills.
But now, what you don't have is
essentially you've just been able to
make one thing at a time. Well, guess
what? Now, we're going to take that one
idea to make a whole month's worth of
content.
Okay. So, to make this challenge work,
I've pre-planned a five kind of step or
five levels to make this work. Okay.
Because I've got a limited amount of
time and trying to do this in less than
30 minutes and I want to do 30 days
worth of content as I don't really care
about this page in one conversation.
Okay. So, I've split this into five
different levels. Focus, style, plan,
create, and package. And I've created
this document which is going to be
available to everyone in my vault which
I'm actually going to use live step by
step which guides us through the entire
process. Okay. So 30 days of content one
conversation. Each phase or each level
is going to give you examples on how to
use it etc. So I deserve a like just for
giving you this and for the way you know
I'm pre-planning everything to help. But
what to give Claude? So our first prompt
is this one here. And the reason we need
to start with focus is this. When we
have a page, when we're using AI with,
you know, it's not just about strategy,
it's that the AI needs kind of context.
It needs an operating system. It needs a
foundation. It needs a a north star, a
goal. And essentially, with most pages
on social media, they're designed to
make money. Okay? And what's the best
way to make money? With this simple
framework right here, you can rechange
or rec-calibrate your business. You have
three parts of this framework. So you
have person, who specifically are we
talking to? Then we have tension. Why?
What do they feel but can't say? Then we
have path. So where does following you
lead? So me no more more not more
motivation content could be a
reparenting journal, a guided community,
therapy adjacent sponsors. Okay. Then
essentially we need to be able to answer
this. You need as a person, whatever
industry you're in, I help person who
feels tension by showing them this path.
If you want to make money on social
media, YouTube, anything, you need to be
able to answer things simply in this
format. And I'm going to help you right
now. Now, what does this look like for
any creator? You could be a fitness
coach, personal brand, business, doesn't
matter. I help busy parents who feel
guilty about taking time for themselves
by giving them permission to prioritize
their health in 20 minutes a day. You
see, this is super intentional. It's
going to allow us to create all of this
content super like specifically and, you
know, actually do some good stuff which
is unique, not generic. Business
creator, I help burnt out freelancers
who've lost control of their time by
building systems that give their life
back. So, there you go. Now, what we're
going to do is scroll down to level one.
So find who you're really serving, what
they actually feel and what you could
build on it. So grab this prompt right
here. Now I've already started and what
you can do is just paste the prompt in
and you basically as you can see here
what to give Claude. You just throw in
some assets you have. So if you have
competitors you can throw some
competitors you like. If you already
have a page you can throw some of your
best performing stuff, your bio,
whatever you have like you can throw in
analytics, anything. Okay. Then you run
the prompt and what you should expect is
a deep breakdown of some of the posts
and then three four directions which are
going to essentially be our focus. Okay,
which is going to really help build this
foundation for the rest of the video. So
you can see right here, you know, it
speaks about the post. I'm going to
scroll down. Then it's going to give me
four directions. So for this one, it's
giving me a faith restoration at scale,
the daily good news network. I'm already
just going to skip that one because I
don't want to do news. Decoded words for
feelings you didn't know you had. So
day-to-day pivot the page towards
Japanese emotions post format. So this
sounds good already aesthetically. I can
imagine it. Who the audience becomes
giving me a brief description. Then the
moment of truth 90-day monetization. I
need to know at this point and so does
the AI. So does everything how we're
going to actually build something from
this. Okay. So and you can see the final
line. I help emotionally articulate
people who can't name what they're
feeling reclaim their inner life by
giving them the words other cultures
already invented. That's actually pretty
cool concept. You know what? Yeah. I
mean, I'm not going to look at these
ones. I'm just going to lock in two,
which I had already done. Lock in number
two. And what will So, you can see here,
pick one direction, lock it in in the
claw convo. Boom. Lock it in. So, the
first decision, pivot or new account.
Don't waste pivot creon. Boom. Boom.
Boom.
Okay, now it's starting to give me some
like, you know, kind of ideas. And this
will be dependent on your model, your
history, and stuff like that if you're
doing this on a new account or
incognito. But essentially, now we're
going to move to level two, which is
super important. So, you don't need to
really interact with that. You need to
just get the information you need and
move on. Because trust me, I've built
this in a way that's going to maximize
everything.
Okay, so the next level is style. And
this is going to allow us to get to
creating content as quickly as possible.
When you don't have a style locked in,
your page will look like crevion, just
all over the place, messy. And to
monetize, you need to have a strong
brand that people remember. So this is
difference. No lock style, random lock
style, clean. Now to have a style, you
want to basically be touching these six
different elements. So palette, figure
style, text treatment, anti-style. So
what is against, you know, stuff that
you don't want in your brand. So it's
important to have this locked in. Now
for this, we're going to go to this
prompt right here. Now for this, you
need something a reference point. So
what I did is I went to Pinterest and
I'm going to go down the Japanese road.
So I typed in, so if I go back, I typed
in Japanese style motivation. Then what
happens on Pinterest, you press one and
it will start showing you loads in that
style and you just kind of go down the
rabbit hole. Now you can get reference
from anywhere and it's super useful
because it's important. You can get
references from logos in real life. You
can get it from YouTube, Instagram,
competitors, your own content, anywhere.
It doesn't matter. Once you have that,
you grab the prompt and head and you can
see here what to give Claude.
Go to here and you I picked about five.
Threw that in here. Now, we're going to
be creating this video wouldn't be
possible without Hicksfield because now
I can create content in Claude with my
Hicksfield connector means I have access
to all the latest image generation
models, video generation models within
Claude, which is insane. So, from
Nanobanana to ChadBt to Nanabanana 99
when it comes out, it will always be
here. Now, now to get access to this,
you it's called Hakesfield MCP. So, you
head over to Higfield. link will be in
the description. You go to MCP and it
will tell you how to install it. So,
open Claude settings. Super easy. You
literally go settings. Then you add the
custom connector. Copy this, sign in,
and it's done. Now you have Hicksfield
in your Clawude chat. And you can see
right here, connectors Hickfield. Boom.
Ready to go. So, I put in my prompt.
Now, with any of these prompts, you can
edit them, add extra stuff. I made sure
to put use Hickfield chat chatbt image 2
and put text on the images. Okay, so I
did that and it came back with these uh
three which don't look bad at all. So
you can see right here using chat GBT
image too don't look bad at all but I
thought I want to take this further. Now
all of these prompts I've built the
plan. It's it's it's prepared but you
can add your own prompts and push back.
And that's exactly what I did right
here. I like all of these, but I want to
have a character throughout my post
which I can build the brand around too
which matches the style and focus. Can
we create some more with this in mind?
And guess what? It came up with the
wanderer. So always seen from behind
three four rear face never visible and
boom. From there it started creating it
and wow these are so much better than
you know these kind of these are this
one I really was impressed as well but
yeah so much better because now it adds
that kind of feel that character so you
can see clean and boom
again right there I mean I don't know
which one I will pick I think this one
is like the most
I'm not sure I don't know I think let's
go for number one so what is the actual
So, what to expect three visuals and
then I guess I need to pick one in. So,
yeah. Okay, let's move over to the next
section once like which is starting to
build this plan. Now, just quickly on
Higsfield, you'll have access to all the
content you make. So, anything that you
make in Claude. So, you know, everything
I make here, I can it will always
automatically go onto my Hicksfield
account, which is where all my assets
and everything are, which is super
useful because then I can, you know,
create more. I can, you know, upscale,
enhance, do anything as well in here,
you know, look at the prompts that, um,
Claude actually used, you know, look at
if I want to change the quality to low,
you know, whatever. So, it's super
useful, but again, you can just stick
inside Claude. So, this is a game
changer. But, let's move over to the
next part, which is going to be the
plan. So you can see right here, focus
style, done, then plan, then we're going
to create. So let's go over to plan.
We'll start building this together cuz
I'm running out of time.
Okay, so now it's starting to plan our
months of content. Now, there's a few
things we need to kind of look at here.
The first thing is on social media, on
YouTube, anywhere, you need to have
series. And that's why it was important
to have our focus part at the beginning
because from that kind of specific
understanding of our you know focus we
can build series and the reason to do
this is we don't want random topics.
Okay random topics attract you know
different people that like tigers then
you post something about a penguin they
like penguins. You need to have some
kind of connectivity between your
content on any platform. when things are
intentional, you're building an
ecosystem, it's predictable, the, you
know, AI makes it predictable as well.
So everything is in sync and even it
kind of fits your sales process as well.
So you know, with the binge loop, this
is another angle. So if you start to
have connecting series and now on
Instagram, you know, you can have
connecting series and stuff like that.
Someone sees part three on their explore
page, you know, that one does really
well. They save it, visits profile, they
find one parts one and two, then they
follow you and it creates this loop when
your content is all kind of connecting.
So, it's super important for us to
understand this right now in our plan.
You know, I'm not just creating 30 days
of random content. I want this to be
purposeful and you know, that's why I
spent time building all of this. So,
this is the prompt right here. I've
already got it. Uh, yeah, I've just
pasted it in the season architect. So
series from the margins credibility
chooses every two weeks words from
minority under translated languages etc.
Words without translations saves okay
and then it has like a focus for each
one calendar May 10th to June the 6th.
Wow. Okay. Wanderer's notebook from the
margins.
Damn.
Okay. Visual variations within the
locked style.
Wow. All from that prompt. what this
month build towards the arch
architecture isn't accidental by June 6
you'll have a character with a in a life
two proof points a weekly okay amazing
so after this a full okay amazing so you
know it's honestly that simple to be
able to kind of build it when you
understand what you're trying to do just
the fact that I want to do 30 days I had
a two three recurring system I had a
style I had something locked in I had a
focus things start to built.
Level five is your packaging. And we've
got a few different things in here. So,
don't think it's just captions cuz trust
me, it's not. And I'm about to blow your
mind with something. But what does ready
supposed to mean? This is not a good
caption. Okay? Very generic. Stay
motivated. Keep pushing forward. You've
got this. No, we want con contextual
captions. Stuff that actually matters,
that actually makes sense, that actually
matches. Claude can only write this
because it's been in the conversation
for every decision. Okay, it's
important. Now, level five package. The
goal, complete posting package, 30
captions, written invoices, schedule,
dates, times, rewritten bio, and I'm
going to create a lead magnet in this
chat. An actual freebie for us to build
our business to take this further. Okay,
so let's go back to the chat. So, the
first prompt I did right here, simple
one, copy and paste. Boom. Write every
caption for the next 30-day calendar.
Each one needs to sound like it's not
comes from a specific page or specific
focus etc. and started to write the CTA
CTA CTA. Now obviously I could give um
you know if you have additional info
like the CTAs you know I want it to be
like keywords for many chat I want it to
be based on this etc. You just add that
variation. Use your secondary tab and do
that. And obviously this is slightly
generic because you know I'm creating a
YouTube video for multiple different
people in different niches to see. But
you know essentially if you can make
small adjustments where it matches your
you know exact requirement it's very
simple to do and it will fit. Okay. So
for this it's doing what I've asked. Now
you can see here. So CTA here it's
telling me the CTA. Save this for the
next time the light surprises you have
the word tag someone whose life you
actually do know you know so it's all
there so let's scroll down and see you
know it kind of came up with all of that
how how the CTAs are distributed across
16 posts so it's giving me that
information super important super useful
what separates these from generic
captions that's very useful now at this
point I wanted to rewrite my bio so you
know this page is just not right now
where it needs to be if I want to do
So I needed to kind of yeah let's take
it up a level. So that's what I did and
it came back with this. So name field to
change to this decoded words English
forgot bio the feelings you've had your
whole life named by every language but
yours one word a week carried by the
wanderer. So of course you know I
wouldn't say that this is an optimal bio
but it is definitely more on brand and
in sync to you know the what I want and
is what I want. Um I would say you know
it could be better but this video isn't
focused necessarily on an Instagram you
know like you know perfectionism. Um but
this is way better and again fits on
brand. What I would say is if there are
bios or you know a bit more information
that you can give here or like goals
then you can add that again you know you
can give reference bios from other pages
etc. But in a in a nutshell this is
super clean. Then we've got to the good
bit which is it decided to create this
le the lexicon. Okay, which is a
link which is a freebie the lead magnet
25 untransatable feelings format PDF
structure and I thought you know it
would create like a three-page document.
they decided to create a 25word
document freebie which has like
different words in different languages
and gives them kind of like context and
stuff like that and it even decided to
create a cover for me. Um so and it even
has actually given me like a kind of
welcome email post download sequence for
my emails etc. If you want me to go more
into like lead magnets, the business
side of things, you know, setting up
like welcome email automations, etc.,
again, let me know. But it's essentially
either one moves you closer to the 4,
7K, 600, 900 m on the 90-day project.
So, there you go. Can you turn it into
an actual document? So, I wanted it to
turn into an actual document. So, it did
that and you should be able to see it
right here. So, you can see
that figure is weird, but again, carried
by the wanderer creon. You can see I
made no like edits or anything to this
and I was extremely surprised by how
clean it is. Like now of course you can
tell that it is created by Claude if you
understand Claude but if with a bit of
editing or with a few improvements in
kind of um prompting it would be
undistinguishable and really really
clean. Okay. Like if I took this to
Canva, made some edits, added some
stuff, but it's insane how it's made.
It's actually did I think, yeah, it did
34 pages. You know, if your audience
likes your page and then they're
downloading this for free and getting
access to this, you know, it's it's a
no-brainer. If you like the full one,
it's coming this summer. You've already
you're already on the list. So, wow. So,
you see lead magnet right there. Um, now
the next thing two was the dashboard. I
wanted to get a visual dashboard of just
everything that we've kind of created so
that we can um
have a look and yeah so let's open this
up right here so you can see so the
decoded system which we've created so
words for decoded complete content
system for the Instagram account
formerly known as crevon um so the focus
the architecture so it's giving me
information about my pallet the wanderer
this is super useful if I decide to hire
people if I decide to move to chat GBT
if I decide to do anything. Having
something like this is kind of a
foundation and super useful in terms of
you know if you ever start to wander
away you know you can see here I've got
three series three jobs you know I can
always get information from this now
with AI the calendar again in the future
I can just spin this around 16 captions
written
all right here from follower to reader
to buyer so I've got the feed I've got
the lexicon I've got the full lexicon if
I wanted to create this so £29 book or
dollar book $7 a month letter bundle
$39. So, it's already given me like a
kind of business plan that could work 90
days from pivot to first revenue floor.
I'm tempted to do this. Should I try
this?
What was built? Everything above came
from one conversation. So, we did the
pivot, the identity, the system, the
calendar, the images, the motion, the
voice, the lexicon, words for feelings,
English forgot. And there we have it.
And there we have it in one chat. If I
scroll all the way up, you will see that
we've been able to create and build this
entire account from scratch again. And
you know, this is the power of, you
know, systemized AI and intentual an
intentional um, you know, strategy like
yeah, you know, this account was
completely dead and now I have a full
system should I want to go ahead with it
with no stone unturned. Okay, so you
have content people want to watch, but
you don't have anything to sell them. So
now let's build the offer, the funnel,
and the emails. Even if you're a
business owner, have clients, whatever.
Do not miss this.
So here we have Life of I, and we're
going to be using this account to run
this experiment or to run this
challenge, building these brains, this
system. This can be done on literally
any account as long as you have a few
posts or you could just use competitors.
If you ever want to be featured in one
of my videos like this creator today, be
sure to just drop your account and any
information and I'll be storing it for
usage in the future. Let's jump back to
the video. So, the first thing we want
to do is grab some screenshots and
you'll see the power of Fable, like how
it's able to do this. So, I grabbed a
few screenshots. You can see right here.
So, I've got the bio. I've got literally
some screenshots of her kind of profile
here. And then I've literally downloaded
one carousel and just put it in then
with my prompt which follows these kind
of rules here about position. So who she
is for whom online voice one line voice
tone rules pallet type world rules. So
this is all going to be available in my
vault. All the prompts that I'm about to
show you to build this brand business
content run. Okay. Now to make this all
happen I've had to connect my Higsfield
to my claude. And Higsfield is my number
one image and video generation platform.
So you can see right here if I press
image I've got Chachi image 2 Nabonana 2
etc. All the latest models anytime they
come here rather than me you know
subscribing to all of them and doing
them all in different places. Everything
can be done right here. The beautiful
thing is this MCP right here. I'm able
to go onto Claude and connect this to it
simply by going to settings or to
customize. right here. I'm able to go to
connectors and literally connect it to
Hicksfield, which means now in my chat
anytime I want, I can just be like
create with Chad Beauty Image 2 or Seed
Dance or whatever. It's the [music]
bridge that connects my Claude to these
powerful image or video generation
tools. Once that's connected, which I
was able to, I've essentially then
started to build this brand and you can
see this whole thing was done here.
Okay, so Life of Eye palette. Boom.
We've got all the hex codes that we
need. Perfect. So, the thing I wanted
was a mood board. And remember, we're
going to keep referencing her page right
here. Mood board. Okay, looks pretty
good. The palette looks good. So, small
tweaks, big focus. It's giving me the
text [music] to use, should use based on
the images that I've shared, etc. And it
looks clean, honestly. Like, that's a
clean start. So, let's see. Let's go
down. And then I have the final kind of
brand brain. So, you can see right here,
master rules document. So, positioning,
Aisha is the techs friend who finds the
features your devices were hiding from
you. Boom. Voice. It's givingven me all
of that just from that information.
Boom. Saved all of that typography, etc.
And all I would do then is save that and
you can store that anywhere. And that's
your kind of brand brain. But now let's
take it further because we're building a
whole system. So essentially one thing
to remember is with all [music] of these
different models, Fable builds the brain
and that's what we're kind of doing with
this chat. Okay. But we're also testing
it, seeing what it can do when I push it
to the limit. So think across everything
at once, executes rules that already
exist. [music] This is Sonet. So, we're
building the rules now and Sonnet and
the other models will be able to execute
them later.
Now, what we want to do is with
business, what are we looking for? One
of the reasons I picked her as well is
she didn't have a product. Okay, so
she's got these million followers, but
she's not monetizing. So, what can we
do? What is Fable going to come up with?
Three directions each rendered as a real
product. It argues like an investor.
Weak ideas die. Um, the offer, product,
audience, price, why it wins. Okay, so
business brain, the product comes from
the brand, not bolted onto it. So let's
see [music] what happens when I give the
prompt. So next the business brain again
this will be in my vault. Let's have a
look at what happens. So what it would
have done first is you can see this is
the output. So the thinking would have
been a lot more complex. The reason I
asked it to do thinking then generate is
because sometimes it could have gone
just to generating random stuff but it
did the thinking. Okay. So three
directions. The lazy girl tech vault. A
one-time digital tool kit. Uh every hack
app shortcut text replacement she's
never ever posted. Organized with a
searchable match green dashboard. Okay.
cozy screen kit aesthetic pack, low
monthly membership. Now the mockups, so
the lazy girl tech and you know another
thing with Fable as well when I'm using
these image generation models etc on
Hicksfield, they're going to be better
because the thought or the process is
better. Okay, this is the cozy screen
kit 30 plus wallpapers and icons. Wow,
that actually looks pretty cool like in
terms of like just fitting the brand and
stuff. Basically building a brand like
business plan deck. Okay, so this is how
the membership would look. Wow. Okay,
member number one. It looks good. All
three are rendered above. Now the part
where I try to kill them. So this is a
commodity and a drowning in free
alternatives. Pinterest gum road. Okay
fine. Memberships are a content
treadmill. Entire brand promises low
effort. Fine. Against the vault. The
honest attacks are the one time have a
revenue ceiling. Yeah. Okay fine. But
the vault wins because it monetizes
proven demand. Saves matches the brand's
loweffort promise on both sides of the
transaction. Perfect. So the lazy gold
tech £24 one time. So that's around $30.
Lifetime updates. All 150 hacks
organized into a matching dashboard from
number one. Okay. Perfect. So let's
actually look at what it kind of gave us
as the brain the product. So on one time
purchased toolkit every hack who's it
for? So it done all of that thinking
decided that it was going to be the lazy
girl tech vault. Then it built kind of
this business brain version one about
this product right here which I think
really does match hip. And you know the
images I was able to create for example
they look good honestly like that one
looks clean. uh you know I could
probably build a website and if I should
build a website or something let me know
in the comments if you want me to go
deeper into any of the brains like I can
easily go deeper into the business brain
you know building a whole [music]
business strategy you know with AI for
your social media etc again let me know
in the comments anything that pops up
I'm always checking comments and I do
write things down so core contents at
launch 152 hacks organized by device
who's it for it the buyer is the saver
the follower 2238 Apple ecosystem who
has saved five of her carousels and
implemented none okay find the core
offer onetime purchase purchase pricing
logic. Okay, so launch window £19, $25,
then 30, etc. Okay, cool. So, it's given
a lot of different information, which is
super important, you know, because it's
it needs to have logic when it's
creating a business strategy.
What's next? The content brain. So, once
we have the branding, [music] we have
the business side, the next part is kind
of building this content around that.
Because if we're going to sell this
product, we need to create some content
that actually sells it, right? So,
pillars, each one lands to the product.
funnel map, reach, trust, [music] sell,
hooks, inner voice from brainer one
formats, real carousels and why. Again,
if you want me to jump into any of
these, all of [music] these are
independently massive topics. I can do
that. Now, the content brain using the
brand brain and business brain build her
content brain. Three to four content
pillars. Each one must connect to why
someone would eventually buy the
product. Super important funnel mapped.
So, a funnel, top of the funnel,
middleunnel, sell, bottom. Essentially,
it it will tell us where this content
sits in and the formats real carousels
etc. Okay, cool. Pillar one, device
betrayal. Your Mac has been doing all of
this the whole time and said nothing.
This makes content creation so much
easier when you get your pillars right.
Pillars are massive because then you can
start rotating. You can be more
strategic. The days where you're like,
what should I post? You can start go
back to your pillars. Go back to the way
your system that you're building. Funnel
map. So real. This is your reach
betrayal carousel whimsy. Okay. Middle
of the funnel. So it's giving me
examples of different kind of content
that serve each part of the funnel. So
your reach, trust, sell. Okay. Okay. So,
this is where you grab people, you build
trust, then you sell to them. Hook
styles. Again, it's giving me hook
styles. Wow. Okay. Formats, what runs
and where? Carousels, reels, stories,
the system in in one line, whims in
betrayal, find them. Setups and receives
make them believe. The save becomes the
sale. Use saved folder. It actually
works. Very interesting. So now once I
have these three done, make the launch
concept. Essentially at this point, it's
about what can we do with these three
brains to build this business. And you
know I've been able to do this in a
matter of minutes which is insane using
fable format study first. So editorial
typos object etc. So let's have a look.
So assignments okay so it's creating
some carousels. So the task I've given
it here we've got those brains. Let's
start creating some content and put your
money where your mouth is. So again
using cakefield charge image two five
whimsical Mac apps that made me close
Tik Tok. And you know it's even done
that kind of branding that we had in one
of the products previously. And
honestly, like if I saw that on this
page, it [music] would not like stand
out. It would fit and look definitely
like it matches. What's your thoughts?
Again, that one exact same. And it again
like kind of has like this branding to
it, the product, etc. And the final one,
what's actually inside the lazy girl
tech vault? Okay, so it's actually
selling something on this one on this
particular carousel, which is very good
because sometimes we know we're scared
to sell. We're not creating content
about our products and boom, it's being
able to do that as one of the three
carousels. At this point, I believe all
three are good. I'm happy with them and
I want it to build it out. So,
essentially, it's able to build out all
of these carousels. So, these are all
the covers of the carousel and then it
builds it out. So, bongo cat and it just
starts going, "Wow." Okay.
Wow.
Wow. Okay. So, is that the CTA as well?
Wow. That's crazy. Okay. So, it even
adds a CTA again on brand different to
the rest of the carousel. Wow, that's
actually real real good. Okay, so the
next carousel
again very similar style. Wow. Okay,
hack libraries. So, copy and paste. Wow,
this is a really good carousel for
selling selling. Like the quality of
this is immense. Like
and you know literally in one prompt
like I haven't put multiple prompts into
this at all. Literally one prompt just
building kind of this flow this system
you're able to get content at this
level. That's absolutely
I'm I'm super impressed with this um for
[music] this this one in particular
because you know we're trying to build a
business. What was the next step? So now
we wanted to launch. Now this is where
it gets a bit more um kind of difficult.
So essentially what it was able to do is
I decided, okay, I'm going to do a
motion graphic. Okay, so like a real.
What options do I have to create reals?
I didn't want to use her face for this
particular video. Um, but kind of what
real could we do? So let's see what it
came up with. For this one, it decided
to do the saved folder intervention. And
these are all motion graphics. Okay,
I've got it to do it in this chat. 150
things your Mac never told you. Again,
this very much fits her vibes of kind of
the content that has performed well. So
you can see here 1,300 5Girl Mac hacks.
So that's pretty good. 600 on this one.
The content brain is named Heropos. It
dramatized by its own behavior to save
rather than product features count. So
let's see. So hey, boom. I did that. I
like when the AI essentially is able to
ask the right questions to me, you know,
cuz again it's important for you to, you
know, be part of the process. Whilst
this is the architect, you are the kind
of buyer, [music] the investor. So you
know, you matter in this process. So I
went with a it's able to then concept
locked decided that it was going to use
C dance style locked etc using my brand
from my brand document style lock to
style lock. So let's see what it came up
with. So
okay so essentially what it actually
came up with was the different um and
then I would have have to connect them
myself on Cap Cut. There would be a way
where I can do this kind of to automate
this where it kind of builds the whole
motion graphic step by step. [music] If
you want me to make a video about that,
again, let me know. But essentially,
what it gave me was the building block.
So, I would download each one one by one
and then be able to [music] just put
them together and I'd have a reel and
essentially it would create each scene.
So, you can see here they're actually
pretty good.
I don't know if [music] you can hear
that.
You know, considering the amount we've
done in this chat and that it's still on
brand, that it still looks really good
is good. Like, this is how the motion
graphic would start.
Okay. And then it would go to the next
one. Extract. Have you tried any? Okay.
Yeah, I'm It makes sense. And then the
final one is
[music]
Wow. Okay. So, yeah, obviously the the
music and stuff doesn't sync. Um, but
that doesn't matter. Like, you could you
have a good strong reel. You could pin
this at the top of the page right here
and that would be okay. Boom. A very
credible, strong reel done right there.
You just literally download them one by
one, put them in Cap Cut, add a song
over it. Done. Okay, so production is
done. The carousel launch reel approved.
So that's a launch ro. Now we turn
everything into operating plan. So
essentially for this, so it's created a
lead magnet at this point. So free mini
vault, page one, 15-minute lazy max
setup, 10 starter hacks. Wow, again that
looks really good on brand. So let's see
what operating plan. So this is my
30-day launch content plan.
Wow. Okay. So then, you know, I would
again take this to Fable and say, "Okay,
let's build. I'm on day two. I'm on day
three. And then I want to schedule it.
Let's build it." And you just go with
like that because you've got these
documents. You've got this set up. So
you can see it keeps going. This is
where it gets incredibly spicy as well.
Emails are a massive part of your
ecosystem if you're trying to profit on
social media. So [music] this is super
important. If you are interested in more
of the back end, the business side of
social media, emails, etc., that engine,
again, let me know in the comments. This
is something that I would love to make
videos about because this [music] is
where you turn your views into actual
income. Now, you can see right here,
it's built the email engine. So, it's
given the lead magnet, a free mini
vault. So, it's come up with that notion
page built in the same dashboard design
as the paid vault. Okay? So, they're
connecting where it's prompted the
actual CTA lines. Okay? It tells you
where to put your CTAs, the opt-in flow.
It then tells me what if I wanted to do
a kind of many chat automation what to
do the three email sequences the system
on one page. Wow. So this is the final
system. So the brand brain sets the look
and voice the business brain sets the
product on offer. The content brain etc.
Email sales the product. Wow. So all
using Fable using the right connector.
Hicksfield gives me the kind of ability
to connect my images and video
generators. So then I'm able to create
these magnificent systems that
completely could change this person's,
you know, way of creating content, the
way they see the content. Remember, if
you want me to dive deeper into any of
the aspects of this video, from the
content brain to brand brain to [music]
the business side to emails, just let me
know in the comments because honestly,
it makes a big difference and it allows
me to understand you guys better. Let's
jump back to the video. And then finally
I asked it to build a dashboard which
looked like this which I really think is
even on brand but it just gives me a
kind of clarity over everything. And if
I scroll down I can drop the final
export into these slots and they're
approved. So crazy. I can just drop
stuff into this and then I can see the
kind of 30 days launch day 15. So the
launch would be here building hype up to
it. These are kind of purposeful things.
You can see the content system you know
how it sets up kind of obviously I can
zoom in a bit and stuff as well. You can
see right here for example content
brain. So what are we looking at this
the content [music] brain is this side
of things here £24 once you know $30
whatever what it does email engine right
here so you can see kind of how it looks
so this is a visual of everything we've
built you know which is extremely
important and extremely useful when
you're [music] building a system with
multiple steps okay because if you have
a team if I want to go to sonet if I
want to do more I can visualize things
clearly here this is a massive win for
anyone when you're using fable you're
building the architecture Okay, the
building blocks. So that then now I know
the days that I'm going to be using
everything. Okay, the days that I'm
going to be posting the product. Now I
can go to Sonic. I can go to Opus. I
don't need to spend credits on Fable
because everything is done already. The
brain, the structure, and I've built it
myself using the power of a tool like
Fable. [music] Fable is going to be a
master planner where we use it
purposefully in our flows. It still is
way cheaper than hiring a freelancer.
Hiring, you know, a strategist,
incredibly cheaper. It's able to operate
at that higher level compared to
different models. Okay, this is a super
important part. Okay, so the tool got
good enough to stop you thinking this is
something that I want everyone to really
pay attention to with AI. Um you know
one of the things is I couldn't make
this course without telling you this is
that you know and I it was a period in
my life where I really struggled with it
as well. Everyone is now able to make
more posts. Okay. But with posting more
because AI has given us this kind of um
ability to create more you know at a
vast scale we're but we still get the
same results. Okay. So how does that
kind of gap? So, we're posting more and
you might have seen this already, which
is why you're on this course. Why you're
posting and then what comes back stays,
you know, virtually the same. So, you
know, why um essentially now everyone
has access to AI. Okay, so before most
content was pretty bad overall, but now
with AI, you know, you can get AI to
analyze, it can do your hooks, it can do
so many different things. So, most
content is is fine. So whilst this is
going up, you know, this is the same
thing for everyone else. And the ceiling
is actually going up too. Okay. So one
thing I want you to really pay attention
to is three things I don't hand over.
Okay? And this is stuff that I've really
learned. Ideas on paper first. So if you
do have any ideas, don't be afraid to
just go to a piece of paper first, a
notepad or even your notes on your
phone, voice over, whatever.
[clears throat] spend some time actually
a few minutes saying that uh thought
process okay whatever it is and then
take that to AI. If you go straight to
AI it you know and say uh I need some
ideas for this or you know you will just
get generic stuff which the internet is
just you know because it's essentially
sourced from the internet. Okay. So most
of us have creative ideas most of us
have unique ideas.
Do not just go straight to AI. Allow
yourself to open your own door. Then
once you go through that door, you can
start to look around and say, "Okay, you
know, I want AI to help me with this
specific part." That's how you start to
stand out. Okay? And your posts don't
just become repetitions and you know,
you're getting the same output every
time. So my goals stay mine. So I decide
what I'm aiming at. I do not let the
output tell me what I should want. Okay?
That's super important. your goals,
anything to do with the kind of yeah
what you're aiming for. Please try to
digest and come up with that yourself.
Uh because AI again does not know you.
You know, yes, it might know, you know,
that you wake up on Mondays and go to
the park for a run, but it doesn't
really know you. Okay? So, please make
sure you do that. My own logic goes in.
So, I add my thinking to what comes
back. I never ship its reasoning as if
it were mine.
logic. I mean, these two are very much
in sync, but the main point here with
all three of these is to really have
boundaries when you're utilizing AI.
Okay. So, you know, you want to make
sure that you are not just, you know,
trusting it essentially like you're not
just okay. Yeah, you're right. Because
it's not right. It's advice. Okay. It's
suggestions. It's to help you. Okay.
It's not, you know, this is it and you
have to do that. Okay? So, always be
kind of trying to identify that the
problem isn't the bad output. It's not
reading it. It will give you something
decent enough that you skim it and post
it. Decent enough is exactly what makes
it dangerous. Okay? Decent is not what
we want to do. You know, don't be
scared. It's better to fail with your
own ex like experimentation than just
throwing this generic stuff out there
which everyone has seen a thousand
times. Okay?
If you never write the hook, you never
learn hooks and then you cannot tell
what its version is weak. You lose the
ability to judge the exact thing you
handed over. Okay? A hook isn't like too
complicated. Okay? hook, you know, is
like the first thing that everyone runs
to and like, "Oh, yes, give me 20
hooks." In reality, a hook, you know,
maybe I'll make a video about hooks.
Should I make a video about hooks? But
like, in reality, it's not like too
complicated. It's just about getting on
social media, getting to the point as
quickly as possible.
Lying is not what you want to do. It's
literally just get to the point as
quickly as possible. Okay?
Now, AI makes it, you decides if it
ships. So, it does the work. And you
saw, you know, right at the beginning of
the video when I spoke about the models,
you know, you've got Fable, the
architect. Fable is not your boss. You
are the boss of this system. It does the
work, you do the thinking, the results
are yours. Okay? So, I want you to treat
this like a business. You, it does the
work for you, but you do the thinking.
Okay? You are the CEO.
Keep this speed. Keep your head.
Everything in this course works, but it
only works if you're in the room. Don't
be one of these people that just wants
to automate everything. Yeah, I want to
do social media, but you know, I don't
really want to do it, so I'm going to go
to the beach and sip some coconut water
and it's going to do everything for me
and I'm going to get rich.
You're in the wrong game because trust
me, it's not going to work like that.
Everyone has that same idea. So, you're
using AI wrong. What we're trying to do
is use AI to enhance our workflows to
save time here to allow me to put my
efforts here. It's honestly that simple.
Okay, so you have all of it, but you
don't have a first step. What you're
going to do after this course finishes,
here's what you're going to do as soon
as you're ready or on Monday. Now,
you've just watched everything roughly
around 3 hours. If you sit down now and
try to do everything, you will get
through half and stop. Here is something
I recommend.
So the first thing I want you to do is
definitely spend about 20 minutes doing
the foundation document. Okay? So
essentially, you know, you've gone
through this, who you are, who it is
for, what you never sound like, that's
the whole job. I do recommend spending
longer than 20 minutes, but I will say
20 minutes is fine. Okay? You know, the
foundation documents, the brain
documents, like the the the brains, the
foundations, that's like the base. You
know, you essentially do that once. So
rushing that, there's literally no point
in that. Okay? So be sure to spend a bit
of time on that. If you want to, I
recommend probably spending one day on
it. Obviously, you can do other stuff,
too. Spend a day and then come back the
next day when you've slept, you know,
you're feeling refreshed and add some
more stuff to it. Then you have the
brand and the visual brain. So you got
colors, fonts, layout, rules. Make sure
to do this fresh when your brain is most
creative. Try not to do this when you're
tired because you want to be able to
bring your own creative energy to it.
And essentially that can take about 30
minutes. Again, connect it. Make one
thing. One carousel you are checking the
brain actually works. Not filling a
calendar. So when it comes to creating
content, it's not going to be easy.
Okay? It's going to take a bit of time.
There's going to be still, even though
you've watched this, there's still going
to be the mistakes. There's still going
to be some understanding. So take your
time with it. Create one by one and
understand that you are learning. Okay,
but essentially this is to make sure
that the brain works and if there is
elements that you want to change, just
make the tweaks. Okay, simply go back to
the project file. It's simple. Okay, so
the rest of the week, one skill, then
one week of content. So pick the job you
repeat most and turn that into a skill.
Essentially, super easy. Then run the
month flow and take a single week out of
it. So we don't want to go straight into
posting a whole month's worth of
content. we just want to create a week's
worth of content or a few days in. Okay,
but essentially once we have this built,
we've got these steps taken care of,
then we can start to see, okay, you know
what, I'm going to spend more time on
this particular aspect. You know, I want
to do more video generation. I need to
create more skills around this or, you
know, I need to maybe do a video a brain
for videos. You know, there's all these
different things that you're going to
develop yourself. The goal of this
course and everything I do is to give
you the kind of ideation, the workflows,
you know, the base to get going because
I can't, you know, do it for everyone.
Uh, but I can give you the fundamentals
or the tools needed for you to achieve
it. Okay? And you can achieve all of
this.
Leave this alone. Okay? So, the business
system, you need an audience before you
have an you start to sell an offer. Now,
if you do have an audience already, then
start running the business system. Okay?
But don't let it kind of doing content,
business, all and you know struggling
with all of it. Like get the content
down first, which is something I always
do because if you don't have content,
you're not really going to be selling
anything. So get that down first, then
you can start on the business, which is
fine. 20 skills, we don't need all 20
skills. We need to just start slowly
picking the ones we want to do. Okay? 20
skills is too many. Okay? Normally,
you'd have like I'd say six to 10 skills
max max max max max max max max max max
max max that you actually use often and
probably a few that you're using often.
Okay, so don't start being ultra
efficient because that's not going to
help. Automating, I know this is
everyone's favorite word right now.
We don't live in a world where you can
just sit back and do nothing. Okay,
social media requires you. It requires
you. Unless you're building an AI
person, etc., which I don't know if
that's going to be the future or not,
but you are super important. Okay, there
are aspects of this and I'll even make
videos about it in the future where you
can automate things, but
try to put in some effort as well
because trust me, once you start getting
things going, it essentially is
automating because now, okay, I've got a
system for captions. I still need to go
there and say, "Okay, I need to do a
caption for this." But instead of me,
you know, spending hours on scripts or
whatever, it can come to me much
quicker. Okay? So, the word automating
is, you know, you need to be careful
with it. It's not, it doesn't just mean
one button and boom, you know, you're
off to the moon. No. Um, so do this day
one, 20 minutes. Nothing else in the
course without works without it. So that
kind of foundation before you open
anything, don't try to build all of it.
And if you only do one thing, do day
one. Set those brains up. Set that
foundation up because trust me, things
are going to start happening as soon as
you make it happen. So we've come to the
end of the course. Now, if you have
enjoyed this, please like and subscribe
as I greatly appreciate that so more
people can watch this video and so that
I can be inclined to make more like
this. Now, this has taken me a while to
put together. And if there's any
particular aspects you want me to dive
deeper into, please let me know in the
comments as I always check the comments
and you know, I get feedback from you,
my audience, um, to create more content
that way. you know what I teach I also
use you know your comments section is a
great way to get information so please
ask your questions and yeah you know
with AI there is going to be a lot of
changes over the next few years but it's
important for us to incorporate it into
our workflows but not to completely rely
on it. I hope this video has been able
to help you. If you want to dive deeper
into building a brand in a different
way, then I recommend watching this
video right here. These two playlists
are also extremely useful. My name is
Alex and I'll see you at the next video.
Let's create smarter.